{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.102","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656552992","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656552992"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" aa8adcce-ec46-4297-93be-26eb6c1f6f85"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.102"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_m-r-d"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.102","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656556450","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656556450"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" aa8adcce-ec46-4297-93be-26eb6c1f6f85"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.102"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_a-m-ch"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.102","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656560181","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656560181"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" aa8adcce-ec46-4297-93be-26eb6c1f6f85"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.102"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_l-m-h"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.102","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656566396","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656566396"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" aa8adcce-ec46-4297-93be-26eb6c1f6f85"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.102"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_l-m-h"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.102","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656572140","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656572140"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" aa8adcce-ec46-4297-93be-26eb6c1f6f85"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.102"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_e-m-g"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.102","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656578614","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656578614"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" aa8adcce-ec46-4297-93be-26eb6c1f6f85"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.102"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_y-k-m"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.102","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656583024","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656583024"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" aa8adcce-ec46-4297-93be-26eb6c1f6f85"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.102"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_z-e-m"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.102","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656588385","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656588385"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" aa8adcce-ec46-4297-93be-26eb6c1f6f85"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.102"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_y-m-h"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.102","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656593241","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656593241"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" aa8adcce-ec46-4297-93be-26eb6c1f6f85"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.102"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_n-m-l"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.102","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656597891","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656597891"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" aa8adcce-ec46-4297-93be-26eb6c1f6f85"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.102"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_m-v-l"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.102","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656601852","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656601852"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" aa8adcce-ec46-4297-93be-26eb6c1f6f85"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.102"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_j-a-m"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.102","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656607576","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656607575"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" aa8adcce-ec46-4297-93be-26eb6c1f6f85"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.102"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_m_j-a-m"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656617353","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656617353"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" c3148dac-0e3e-4e76-b37e-6f66d242f4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656617577","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656617577"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" c3148dac-0e3e-4e76-b37e-6f66d242f4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656618556","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656618555"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" c3148dac-0e3e-4e76-b37e-6f66d242f4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656619832","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656619832"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" c3148dac-0e3e-4e76-b37e-6f66d242f4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656622683","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656622682"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" c3148dac-0e3e-4e76-b37e-6f66d242f4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656623533","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656623532"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" c3148dac-0e3e-4e76-b37e-6f66d242f4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656623861","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656623860"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" c3148dac-0e3e-4e76-b37e-6f66d242f4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656625104","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656625104"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" c3148dac-0e3e-4e76-b37e-6f66d242f4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656628594","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656628594"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" c3148dac-0e3e-4e76-b37e-6f66d242f4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656629591","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656629591"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" c3148dac-0e3e-4e76-b37e-6f66d242f4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656629857","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656629857"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" c3148dac-0e3e-4e76-b37e-6f66d242f4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656630800","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656630800"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" c3148dac-0e3e-4e76-b37e-6f66d242f4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656633604","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656633604"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" c3148dac-0e3e-4e76-b37e-6f66d242f4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656634641","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656634640"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" c3148dac-0e3e-4e76-b37e-6f66d242f4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656635114","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656635114"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" c3148dac-0e3e-4e76-b37e-6f66d242f4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656639617","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656639616"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" c3148dac-0e3e-4e76-b37e-6f66d242f4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_24"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656639678","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656639678"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" c3148dac-0e3e-4e76-b37e-6f66d242f4ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656647307","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656647307"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 5e70eda7-32c9-4bec-a8d3-f1ae51bbc83b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_n-a-m"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656650965","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656650965"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 5e70eda7-32c9-4bec-a8d3-f1ae51bbc83b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_m-l-u"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656655095","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656655095"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 5e70eda7-32c9-4bec-a8d3-f1ae51bbc83b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_y-v-m"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656658187","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656658187"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 5e70eda7-32c9-4bec-a8d3-f1ae51bbc83b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_m-t-o"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656661110","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656661110"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 5e70eda7-32c9-4bec-a8d3-f1ae51bbc83b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_m-o-r"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656664641","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656664641"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 5e70eda7-32c9-4bec-a8d3-f1ae51bbc83b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_r-m-v"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656668426","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656668425"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 5e70eda7-32c9-4bec-a8d3-f1ae51bbc83b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_f-t-m"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656672032","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656672032"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 5e70eda7-32c9-4bec-a8d3-f1ae51bbc83b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_w-b-m"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656675408","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656675408"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 5e70eda7-32c9-4bec-a8d3-f1ae51bbc83b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_h-v-m"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656679461","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656679461"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 5e70eda7-32c9-4bec-a8d3-f1ae51bbc83b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_g-m-s"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656685204","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656685204"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 5e70eda7-32c9-4bec-a8d3-f1ae51bbc83b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_m_g-m-s"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656694128","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656694128"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 5e70eda7-32c9-4bec-a8d3-f1ae51bbc83b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_m_g-m-s"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656704144","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656704144"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" beee4e96-977c-4727-94be-e94720531531"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656706788","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656706788"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" beee4e96-977c-4727-94be-e94720531531"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656708325","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656708325"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" beee4e96-977c-4727-94be-e94720531531"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656711588","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656711588"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" beee4e96-977c-4727-94be-e94720531531"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656713150","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656713150"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" beee4e96-977c-4727-94be-e94720531531"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656716203","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656716202"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" beee4e96-977c-4727-94be-e94720531531"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656717766","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656717766"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" beee4e96-977c-4727-94be-e94720531531"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656719833","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656719833"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" beee4e96-977c-4727-94be-e94720531531"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656721384","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656721384"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" beee4e96-977c-4727-94be-e94720531531"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656724593","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656724592"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" beee4e96-977c-4727-94be-e94720531531"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656726168","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656726168"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" beee4e96-977c-4727-94be-e94720531531"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656735585","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656735585"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" beee4e96-977c-4727-94be-e94720531531"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656735683","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656735683"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" beee4e96-977c-4727-94be-e94720531531"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656745367","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656745366"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITUO"," userResponse":" KITUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656745990","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656745990"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIDOGO"," userResponse":" KIDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656746212","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656746212"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656746908","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656746908"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MABASI"," userResponse":" MABASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656747680","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656747679"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJINI"," userResponse":" KIJIJINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656748207","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656748207"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWETU"," userResponse":" MWETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656749320","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656749319"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILIJAA"," userResponse":" KILIJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656750258","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656750257"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHUGHULI"," userResponse":" SHUGHULI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656750663","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656750663"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656751112","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656751111"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656751325","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656751324"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656752048","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656752048"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MABASI"," userResponse":" MABASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656754314","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656754313"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chini palikuwa na mizigo zaidi ya kupakia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656754760","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656754759"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chini palikuwa na mizigo zaidi ya kupakia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGI"," userResponse":" NYINGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656755555","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656755555"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chini palikuwa na mizigo zaidi ya kupakia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ZILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656756470","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656756470"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chini palikuwa na mizigo zaidi ya kupakia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIMEJAZA"," userResponse":" ZIMEJAZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656757327","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656757327"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chini palikuwa na mizigo zaidi ya kupakia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIZIGO"," userResponse":" MIZIGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656759845","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656759845"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chini palikuwa na mizigo zaidi ya kupakia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656760673","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656760673"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chini palikuwa na mizigo zaidi ya kupakia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIKUWA"," userResponse":" PALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656760910","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656760909"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chini palikuwa na mizigo zaidi ya kupakia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656761605","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656761605"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chini palikuwa na mizigo zaidi ya kupakia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIZIGO"," userResponse":" MIZIGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656762307","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656762306"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chini palikuwa na mizigo zaidi ya kupakia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656762403","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656762403"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chini palikuwa na mizigo zaidi ya kupakia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656763223","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656763222"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chini palikuwa na mizigo zaidi ya kupakia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPAKIA"," userResponse":" KUPAKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656766037","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656766037"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kondakta waliita majina tofauti ya mahali basi zilielekea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KONDAKTA"," userResponse":" KONDAKTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656766961","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656766961"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kondakta waliita majina tofauti ya mahali basi zilielekea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIITA"," userResponse":" WALIITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656767711","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656767710"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kondakta waliita majina tofauti ya mahali basi zilielekea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJINA"," userResponse":" MAJINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656768739","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656768739"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kondakta waliita majina tofauti ya mahali basi zilielekea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOFAUTI"," userResponse":" TOFAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656768855","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656768855"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kondakta waliita majina tofauti ya mahali basi zilielekea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656769657","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656769657"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kondakta waliita majina tofauti ya mahali basi zilielekea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHALI"," userResponse":" MAHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656770388","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656770388"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kondakta waliita majina tofauti ya mahali basi zilielekea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656771582","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656771581"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kondakta waliita majina tofauti ya mahali basi zilielekea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZILIELEKEA"," userResponse":" ZILIELEKEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656774815","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656774813"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenda magharibi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIJI"," userResponse":" JIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656777585","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656777585"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenda magharibi!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIJI"," userResponse":" JIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656779905","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656779904"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenda magharibi!"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656780932","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656780932"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenda magharibi!"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAGHARIBI"," userResponse":" MAGHARIBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656783862","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656783862"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilisikia kondakta akiita kwa sauti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILISIKIA"," userResponse":" NILISIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656784657","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656784656"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilisikia kondakta akiita kwa sauti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KONDAKTA"," userResponse":" KONDAKTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656785432","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656785432"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilisikia kondakta akiita kwa sauti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIITA"," userResponse":" AKIITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656785689","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656785689"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilisikia kondakta akiita kwa sauti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656786313","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656786312"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilisikia kondakta akiita kwa sauti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656788736","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656788735"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ndiyo basi niliyohitaji kupanda kwa usafiri wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" ILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656789197","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656789197"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ndiyo basi niliyohitaji kupanda kwa usafiri wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIYO"," userResponse":" NDIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656789694","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656789693"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ndiyo basi niliyohitaji kupanda kwa usafiri wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656790780","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656790779"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ndiyo basi niliyohitaji kupanda kwa usafiri wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIYOHITAJI"," userResponse":" NILIYOHITAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656791604","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656791604"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ndiyo basi niliyohitaji kupanda kwa usafiri wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPANDA"," userResponse":" KUPANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656792115","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656792115"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ndiyo basi niliyohitaji kupanda kwa usafiri wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656792835","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656792834"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ndiyo basi niliyohitaji kupanda kwa usafiri wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USAFIRI"," userResponse":" USAFIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656793296","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656793296"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ndiyo basi niliyohitaji kupanda kwa usafiri wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656796110","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656796109"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kwenda jijini lilikuwa karibu kujaa lakini watu zaidi walijishughulisha kutaka kupanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656796275","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656796274"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kwenda jijini lilikuwa karibu kujaa lakini watu zaidi walijishughulisha kutaka kupanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656796765","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656796765"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kwenda jijini lilikuwa karibu kujaa lakini watu zaidi walijishughulisha kutaka kupanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656797447","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656797446"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kwenda jijini lilikuwa karibu kujaa lakini watu zaidi walijishughulisha kutaka kupanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIJINI"," userResponse":" JIJINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656798100","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656798100"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kwenda jijini lilikuwa karibu kujaa lakini watu zaidi walijishughulisha kutaka kupanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIKUWA"," userResponse":" LILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656798759","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656798759"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kwenda jijini lilikuwa karibu kujaa lakini watu zaidi walijishughulisha kutaka kupanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" KARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656799374","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656799373"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kwenda jijini lilikuwa karibu kujaa lakini watu zaidi walijishughulisha kutaka kupanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUJAA"," userResponse":" KUJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656800209","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656800208"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kwenda jijini lilikuwa karibu kujaa lakini watu zaidi walijishughulisha kutaka kupanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656800611","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656800611"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kwenda jijini lilikuwa karibu kujaa lakini watu zaidi walijishughulisha kutaka kupanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656801401","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656801400"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kwenda jijini lilikuwa karibu kujaa lakini watu zaidi walijishughulisha kutaka kupanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656803150","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656803150"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kwenda jijini lilikuwa karibu kujaa lakini watu zaidi walijishughulisha kutaka kupanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIJISHUGHULISHA"," userResponse":" WALIJISHUGHULISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656803945","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656803944"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kwenda jijini lilikuwa karibu kujaa lakini watu zaidi walijishughulisha kutaka kupanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTAKA"," userResponse":" KUTAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656804647","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656804647"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kwenda jijini lilikuwa karibu kujaa lakini watu zaidi walijishughulisha kutaka kupanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPANDA"," userResponse":" KUPANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656807191","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656807191"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine waliiweka katika sehemu ya juu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADHI"," userResponse":" BAADHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656807555","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656807555"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine waliiweka katika sehemu ya juu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAO"," userResponse":" YAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656808596","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656808595"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine waliiweka katika sehemu ya juu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPAKIA"," userResponse":" WALIPAKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656809471","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656809470"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine waliiweka katika sehemu ya juu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIZIGO"," userResponse":" MIZIGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656810191","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656810190"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine waliiweka katika sehemu ya juu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656810329","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656810329"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine waliiweka katika sehemu ya juu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656810822","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656810822"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine waliiweka katika sehemu ya juu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656813359","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656813359"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine waliiweka katika sehemu ya juu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656814383","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656814383"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine waliiweka katika sehemu ya juu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIIWEKA"," userResponse":" WALIIWEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656814935","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656814935"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine waliiweka katika sehemu ya juu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656815696","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656815695"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine waliiweka katika sehemu ya juu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SEHEMU"," userResponse":" SEHEMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656815828","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656815828"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine waliiweka katika sehemu ya juu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656816172","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656816171"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine waliiweka katika sehemu ya juu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656819419","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656819419"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Abiria wapya walishika tiketi zao huku wakitafuta mahali pa kukaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ABIRIA"," userResponse":" ABIRIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656819982","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656819982"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Abiria wapya walishika tiketi zao huku wakitafuta mahali pa kukaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAPYA"," userResponse":" WAPYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656820756","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656820755"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Abiria wapya walishika tiketi zao huku wakitafuta mahali pa kukaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALISHIKA"," userResponse":" WALISHIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656821265","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656821264"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Abiria wapya walishika tiketi zao huku wakitafuta mahali pa kukaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TIKETI"," userResponse":" TIKETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656821923","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656821923"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Abiria wapya walishika tiketi zao huku wakitafuta mahali pa kukaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAO"," userResponse":" ZAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656822632","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656822632"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Abiria wapya walishika tiketi zao huku wakitafuta mahali pa kukaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" HUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656823600","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656823599"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Abiria wapya walishika tiketi zao huku wakitafuta mahali pa kukaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKITAFUTA"," userResponse":" WAKITAFUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656824166","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656824166"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Abiria wapya walishika tiketi zao huku wakitafuta mahali pa kukaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHALI"," userResponse":" MAHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656824378","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656824377"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Abiria wapya walishika tiketi zao huku wakitafuta mahali pa kukaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PA"," userResponse":" PA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656825030","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656825029"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Abiria wapya walishika tiketi zao huku wakitafuta mahali pa kukaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKAA"," userResponse":" KUKAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656827776","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656827776"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanawake waliokuwa na watoto wadogo waliwatayarisha kwa safari hiyo ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAWAKE"," userResponse":" WANAWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656828632","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656828631"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanawake waliokuwa na watoto wadogo waliwatayarisha kwa safari hiyo ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIOKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656828894","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656828894"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanawake waliokuwa na watoto wadogo waliwatayarisha kwa safari hiyo ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656829502","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656829502"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanawake waliokuwa na watoto wadogo waliwatayarisha kwa safari hiyo ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656830127","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656830127"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanawake waliokuwa na watoto wadogo waliwatayarisha kwa safari hiyo ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WADOGO"," userResponse":" WADOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656831813","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656831812"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanawake waliokuwa na watoto wadogo waliwatayarisha kwa safari hiyo ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIWATAYARISHA"," userResponse":" WALIWATAYARISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656831994","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656831993"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanawake waliokuwa na watoto wadogo waliwatayarisha kwa safari hiyo ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656832621","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656832620"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanawake waliokuwa na watoto wadogo waliwatayarisha kwa safari hiyo ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAFARI"," userResponse":" SAFARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656832988","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656832988"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanawake waliokuwa na watoto wadogo waliwatayarisha kwa safari hiyo ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656833351","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656833351"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanawake waliokuwa na watoto wadogo waliwatayarisha kwa safari hiyo ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEFU"," userResponse":" NDEFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656837128","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656837127"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilipenyeza ndani nikakaa karibu na dirisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIPENYEZA"," userResponse":" NILIPENYEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656837668","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656837667"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilipenyeza ndani nikakaa karibu na dirisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" NDANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656838461","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656838460"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilipenyeza ndani nikakaa karibu na dirisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIKAKAA"," userResponse":" NIKAKAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656839015","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656839015"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilipenyeza ndani nikakaa karibu na dirisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" KARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656839191","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656839189"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilipenyeza ndani nikakaa karibu na dirisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656839804","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656839804"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilipenyeza ndani nikakaa karibu na dirisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DIRISHA"," userResponse":" DIRISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656842149","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656842148"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu aliyeketi karibu nami alishika mfuko wa plastiki wa kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTU"," userResponse":" MTU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656842987","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656842987"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu aliyeketi karibu nami alishika mfuko wa plastiki wa kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEKETI"," userResponse":" ALIYEKETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656843514","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656843513"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu aliyeketi karibu nami alishika mfuko wa plastiki wa kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" KARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656844108","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656844108"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu aliyeketi karibu nami alishika mfuko wa plastiki wa kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAMI"," userResponse":" NAMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656844999","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656844998"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu aliyeketi karibu nami alishika mfuko wa plastiki wa kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISHIKA"," userResponse":" ALISHIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656845538","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656845537"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu aliyeketi karibu nami alishika mfuko wa plastiki wa kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFUKO"," userResponse":" MFUKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656845793","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656845793"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu aliyeketi karibu nami alishika mfuko wa plastiki wa kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656846696","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656846696"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu aliyeketi karibu nami alishika mfuko wa plastiki wa kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PLASTIKI"," userResponse":" PLASTIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656847114","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656847113"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu aliyeketi karibu nami alishika mfuko wa plastiki wa kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656847671","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656847671"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu aliyeketi karibu nami alishika mfuko wa plastiki wa kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJANI"," userResponse":" KIJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656848370","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656848369"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu aliyeketi karibu nami alishika mfuko wa plastiki wa kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBICHI"," userResponse":" KIBICHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656850979","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656850979"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivaa viatu vilivyozeeka koti kuukuu na alionekana kuwa na wasiwasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIVAA"," userResponse":" ALIVAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656851967","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656851967"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivaa viatu vilivyozeeka koti kuukuu na alionekana kuwa na wasiwasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIATU"," userResponse":" VIATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656852911","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656852910"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivaa viatu vilivyozeeka koti kuukuu na alionekana kuwa na wasiwasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILIVYOZEEKA"," userResponse":" VILIVYOZEEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656853721","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656853720"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivaa viatu vilivyozeeka koti kuukuu na alionekana kuwa na wasiwasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOTI"," userResponse":" KOTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656854336","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656854335"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivaa viatu vilivyozeeka koti kuukuu na alionekana kuwa na wasiwasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUUKUU"," userResponse":" KUUKUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656855089","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656855088"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivaa viatu vilivyozeeka koti kuukuu na alionekana kuwa na wasiwasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656856152","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656856152"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivaa viatu vilivyozeeka koti kuukuu na alionekana kuwa na wasiwasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIONEKANA"," userResponse":" ALIONEKANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656856555","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656856554"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivaa viatu vilivyozeeka koti kuukuu na alionekana kuwa na wasiwasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656856828","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656856827"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivaa viatu vilivyozeeka koti kuukuu na alionekana kuwa na wasiwasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656857591","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656857591"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivaa viatu vilivyozeeka koti kuukuu na alionekana kuwa na wasiwasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WASIWASI"," userResponse":" WASIWASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656861020","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656861020"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliangalia nje na kutambua kwamba nilikuwa naondoka kijijini mwangu mahali ambapo nililelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIANGALIA"," userResponse":" NILIANGALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656861667","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656861666"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliangalia nje na kutambua kwamba nilikuwa naondoka kijijini mwangu mahali ambapo nililelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJE"," userResponse":" NJE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656862136","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656862135"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliangalia nje na kutambua kwamba nilikuwa naondoka kijijini mwangu mahali ambapo nililelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656862947","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656862947"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliangalia nje na kutambua kwamba nilikuwa naondoka kijijini mwangu mahali ambapo nililelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTAMBUA"," userResponse":" KUTAMBUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656863677","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656863677"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliangalia nje na kutambua kwamba nilikuwa naondoka kijijini mwangu mahali ambapo nililelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" KWAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656864759","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656864758"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliangalia nje na kutambua kwamba nilikuwa naondoka kijijini mwangu mahali ambapo nililelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIKUWA"," userResponse":" NILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656865633","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656865633"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliangalia nje na kutambua kwamba nilikuwa naondoka kijijini mwangu mahali ambapo nililelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAONDOKA"," userResponse":" NAONDOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656866497","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656866497"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliangalia nje na kutambua kwamba nilikuwa naondoka kijijini mwangu mahali ambapo nililelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJINI"," userResponse":" KIJIJINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656867272","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656867272"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliangalia nje na kutambua kwamba nilikuwa naondoka kijijini mwangu mahali ambapo nililelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANGU"," userResponse":" MWANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656868068","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656868067"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliangalia nje na kutambua kwamba nilikuwa naondoka kijijini mwangu mahali ambapo nililelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHALI"," userResponse":" MAHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656868713","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656868713"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliangalia nje na kutambua kwamba nilikuwa naondoka kijijini mwangu mahali ambapo nililelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBAPO"," userResponse":" AMBAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656869793","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656869792"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliangalia nje na kutambua kwamba nilikuwa naondoka kijijini mwangu mahali ambapo nililelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILILELEWA"," userResponse":" NILILELEWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656872416","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656872414"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa naenda katika jiji kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIKUWA"," userResponse":" NILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656873058","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656873058"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa naenda katika jiji kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAENDA"," userResponse":" NAENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656873672","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656873671"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa naenda katika jiji kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656874121","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656874120"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa naenda katika jiji kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIJI"," userResponse":" JIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656874718","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656874717"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa naenda katika jiji kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656878170","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656878170"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upakiaji mizigo ulikamilika na abiria wakawa wameketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPAKIAJI"," userResponse":" UPAKIAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656878823","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656878823"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upakiaji mizigo ulikamilika na abiria wakawa wameketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIZIGO"," userResponse":" MIZIGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656880297","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656880297"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upakiaji mizigo ulikamilika na abiria wakawa wameketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIKAMILIKA"," userResponse":" ULIKAMILIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656880901","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656880901"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upakiaji mizigo ulikamilika na abiria wakawa wameketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656881564","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656881564"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upakiaji mizigo ulikamilika na abiria wakawa wameketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ABIRIA"," userResponse":" ABIRIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656882167","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656882166"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upakiaji mizigo ulikamilika na abiria wakawa wameketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAWA"," userResponse":" WAKAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656883105","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656883104"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upakiaji mizigo ulikamilika na abiria wakawa wameketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAMEKETI"," userResponse":" WAMEKETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656885972","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656885972"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WACHUUZI"," userResponse":" WACHUUZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656886872","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656886872"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIZIDI"," userResponse":" WALIZIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656888133","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656888133"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSUKUMANA"," userResponse":" KUSUKUMANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656889173","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656889173"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTAKA"," userResponse":" KUTAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656889952","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656889951"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUINGIA"," userResponse":" KUINGIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656890569","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656890568"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" NDANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656890734","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656890734"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656891349","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656891348"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656892069","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656892068"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILI"," userResponse":" ILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656892586","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656892586"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAUZE"," userResponse":" WAUZE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656893203","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656893203"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BIDHAA"," userResponse":" BIDHAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656893711","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656893710"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAO"," userResponse":" ZAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656895902","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656895901"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656896690","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656896690"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656897823","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656897823"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITAJA"," userResponse":" ALITAJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656898034","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656898034"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656898812","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656898812"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656899666","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656899665"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJINA"," userResponse":" MAJINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656899990","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656899989"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656900603","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656900603"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BIDHAA"," userResponse":" BIDHAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656901599","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656901599"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIVYOKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIVYOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656902372","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656902371"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAUZA"," userResponse":" ANAUZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656904814","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656904814"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maneno yao yalinifurahisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANENO"," userResponse":" MANENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656905262","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656905261"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maneno yao yalinifurahisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAO"," userResponse":" YAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656906639","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656906639"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maneno yao yalinifurahisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALINIFURAHISHA"," userResponse":" YALINIFURAHISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656909606","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656909606"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya abiria walinunua vinywaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADHI"," userResponse":" BAADHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656909759","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656909759"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya abiria walinunua vinywaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656910570","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656910569"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya abiria walinunua vinywaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ABIRIA"," userResponse":" ABIRIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656911902","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656911902"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya abiria walinunua vinywaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALINUNUA"," userResponse":" WALINUNUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656912706","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656912704"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya abiria walinunua vinywaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VINYWAJI"," userResponse":" VINYWAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656915261","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656915261"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine wakanunua vitafunaji vidogo na kuanza kutafuna."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656916256","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656916255"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine wakanunua vitafunaji vidogo na kuanza kutafuna."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKANUNUA"," userResponse":" WAKANUNUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656917389","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656917389"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine wakanunua vitafunaji vidogo na kuanza kutafuna."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITAFUNAJI"," userResponse":" VITAFUNAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656918176","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656918175"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine wakanunua vitafunaji vidogo na kuanza kutafuna."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIDOGO"," userResponse":" VIDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656918605","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656918605"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine wakanunua vitafunaji vidogo na kuanza kutafuna."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656919219","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656919218"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine wakanunua vitafunaji vidogo na kuanza kutafuna."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUANZA"," userResponse":" KUANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656920128","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656920128"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine wakanunua vitafunaji vidogo na kuanza kutafuna."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTAFUNA"," userResponse":" KUTAFUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656922949","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656922949"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasiokuwa na fedha kama mimi walitazama tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WASIOKUWA"," userResponse":" WASIOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656923164","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656923164"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasiokuwa na fedha kama mimi walitazama tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656923748","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656923747"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasiokuwa na fedha kama mimi walitazama tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FEDHA"," userResponse":" FEDHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656924432","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656924431"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasiokuwa na fedha kama mimi walitazama tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656925099","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656925098"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasiokuwa na fedha kama mimi walitazama tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656926228","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656926228"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasiokuwa na fedha kama mimi walitazama tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALITAZAMA"," userResponse":" WALITAZAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656926631","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656926631"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasiokuwa na fedha kama mimi walitazama tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TU"," userResponse":" TU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656929780","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656929780"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shughuli hizi zilikatizwa kwa mlio wa honi ya basi ishara kwamba tulikuwa tayari kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHUGHULI"," userResponse":" SHUGHULI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656930103","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656930103"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shughuli hizi zilikatizwa kwa mlio wa honi ya basi ishara kwamba tulikuwa tayari kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIZI"," userResponse":" HIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656931146","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656931145"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shughuli hizi zilikatizwa kwa mlio wa honi ya basi ishara kwamba tulikuwa tayari kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZILIKATIZWA"," userResponse":" ZILIKATIZWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656931365","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656931365"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shughuli hizi zilikatizwa kwa mlio wa honi ya basi ishara kwamba tulikuwa tayari kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656931818","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656931818"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shughuli hizi zilikatizwa kwa mlio wa honi ya basi ishara kwamba tulikuwa tayari kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLIO"," userResponse":" MLIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656932131","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656932131"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shughuli hizi zilikatizwa kwa mlio wa honi ya basi ishara kwamba tulikuwa tayari kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656932695","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656932694"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shughuli hizi zilikatizwa kwa mlio wa honi ya basi ishara kwamba tulikuwa tayari kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HONI"," userResponse":" HONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656933188","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656933187"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shughuli hizi zilikatizwa kwa mlio wa honi ya basi ishara kwamba tulikuwa tayari kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656933744","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656933743"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shughuli hizi zilikatizwa kwa mlio wa honi ya basi ishara kwamba tulikuwa tayari kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656934625","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656934624"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shughuli hizi zilikatizwa kwa mlio wa honi ya basi ishara kwamba tulikuwa tayari kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ISHARA"," userResponse":" ISHARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656935241","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656935241"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shughuli hizi zilikatizwa kwa mlio wa honi ya basi ishara kwamba tulikuwa tayari kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" KWAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656936207","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656936207"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shughuli hizi zilikatizwa kwa mlio wa honi ya basi ishara kwamba tulikuwa tayari kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIKUWA"," userResponse":" TULIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656937075","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656937074"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shughuli hizi zilikatizwa kwa mlio wa honi ya basi ishara kwamba tulikuwa tayari kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAYARI"," userResponse":" TAYARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656937956","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656937956"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shughuli hizi zilikatizwa kwa mlio wa honi ya basi ishara kwamba tulikuwa tayari kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUONDOKA"," userResponse":" KUONDOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656940826","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656940826"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kondakta aliwataka wachuuzi kuondoka ndani ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KONDAKTA"," userResponse":" KONDAKTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656941749","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656941748"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kondakta aliwataka wachuuzi kuondoka ndani ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWATAKA"," userResponse":" ALIWATAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656942565","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656942565"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kondakta aliwataka wachuuzi kuondoka ndani ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WACHUUZI"," userResponse":" WACHUUZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656943365","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656943364"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kondakta aliwataka wachuuzi kuondoka ndani ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUONDOKA"," userResponse":" KUONDOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656943891","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656943890"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kondakta aliwataka wachuuzi kuondoka ndani ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" NDANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656944010","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656944010"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kondakta aliwataka wachuuzi kuondoka ndani ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656944522","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656944521"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kondakta aliwataka wachuuzi kuondoka ndani ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656947644","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656947644"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wachuuzi walisukumana huku wakitafuta njia ya kushuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WACHUUZI"," userResponse":" WACHUUZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656948888","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656948888"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wachuuzi walisukumana huku wakitafuta njia ya kushuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALISUKUMANA"," userResponse":" WALISUKUMANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656949579","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656949578"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wachuuzi walisukumana huku wakitafuta njia ya kushuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" HUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656950752","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656950752"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wachuuzi walisukumana huku wakitafuta njia ya kushuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKITAFUTA"," userResponse":" WAKITAFUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656951207","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656951207"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wachuuzi walisukumana huku wakitafuta njia ya kushuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIA"," userResponse":" NJIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656951451","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656951450"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wachuuzi walisukumana huku wakitafuta njia ya kushuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656952184","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656952181"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wachuuzi walisukumana huku wakitafuta njia ya kushuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSHUKA"," userResponse":" KUSHUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656954628","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656954627"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine wao waliwarudisha abiria masalio ya hela zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656955273","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656955273"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine wao waliwarudisha abiria masalio ya hela zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAO"," userResponse":" WAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656956697","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656956696"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine wao waliwarudisha abiria masalio ya hela zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIWARUDISHA"," userResponse":" WALIWARUDISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656957451","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656957451"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine wao waliwarudisha abiria masalio ya hela zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ABIRIA"," userResponse":" ABIRIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656958306","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656958305"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine wao waliwarudisha abiria masalio ya hela zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASALIO"," userResponse":" MASALIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656958567","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656958566"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine wao waliwarudisha abiria masalio ya hela zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656959012","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656959012"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine wao waliwarudisha abiria masalio ya hela zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HELA"," userResponse":" HELA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656959511","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656959509"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine wao waliwarudisha abiria masalio ya hela zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAO"," userResponse":" ZAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656961961","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656961960"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine walifanya juhudi za mwisho kuuza bidhaa zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656962779","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656962778"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine walifanya juhudi za mwisho kuuza bidhaa zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIFANYA"," userResponse":" WALIFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656963443","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656963443"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine walifanya juhudi za mwisho kuuza bidhaa zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUHUDI"," userResponse":" JUHUDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656963692","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656963691"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine walifanya juhudi za mwisho kuuza bidhaa zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656964338","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656964337"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine walifanya juhudi za mwisho kuuza bidhaa zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWISHO"," userResponse":" MWISHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656965148","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656965148"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine walifanya juhudi za mwisho kuuza bidhaa zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUUZA"," userResponse":" KUUZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656965740","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656965740"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine walifanya juhudi za mwisho kuuza bidhaa zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BIDHAA"," userResponse":" BIDHAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656966209","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656966208"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine walifanya juhudi za mwisho kuuza bidhaa zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAO"," userResponse":" ZAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656969157","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656969156"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi lilipoondoka kituoni nilichungulia dirishani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656970471","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656970471"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi lilipoondoka kituoni nilichungulia dirishani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIPOONDOKA"," userResponse":" LILIPOONDOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656971470","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656971470"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi lilipoondoka kituoni nilichungulia dirishani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITUONI"," userResponse":" KITUONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656972878","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656972877"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi lilipoondoka kituoni nilichungulia dirishani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILICHUNGULIA"," userResponse":" NILICHUNGULIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656973702","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656973701"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi lilipoondoka kituoni nilichungulia dirishani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DIRISHANI"," userResponse":" DIRISHANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656976755","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656976755"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilijiuliza ikiwa ningewahi kwenda kijijini mwangu tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIJIULIZA"," userResponse":" NILIJIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656977328","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656977327"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilijiuliza ikiwa ningewahi kwenda kijijini mwangu tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKIWA"," userResponse":" IKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656978141","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656978140"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilijiuliza ikiwa ningewahi kwenda kijijini mwangu tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINGEWAHI"," userResponse":" NINGEWAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656978765","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656978764"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilijiuliza ikiwa ningewahi kwenda kijijini mwangu tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656979569","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656979569"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilijiuliza ikiwa ningewahi kwenda kijijini mwangu tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJINI"," userResponse":" KIJIJINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656980035","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656980035"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilijiuliza ikiwa ningewahi kwenda kijijini mwangu tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANGU"," userResponse":" MWANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656980631","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656980631"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilijiuliza ikiwa ningewahi kwenda kijijini mwangu tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656984091","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656984090"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safari ilipoendelea joto lilikuwa jingi ndani ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAFARI"," userResponse":" SAFARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656985421","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656985421"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safari ilipoendelea joto lilikuwa jingi ndani ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIPOENDELEA"," userResponse":" ILIPOENDELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656986407","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656986407"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safari ilipoendelea joto lilikuwa jingi ndani ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JOTO"," userResponse":" JOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656987157","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656987157"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safari ilipoendelea joto lilikuwa jingi ndani ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIKUWA"," userResponse":" LILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656987996","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656987996"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safari ilipoendelea joto lilikuwa jingi ndani ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JINGI"," userResponse":" JINGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656988494","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656988494"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safari ilipoendelea joto lilikuwa jingi ndani ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" NDANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656988615","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656988615"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safari ilipoendelea joto lilikuwa jingi ndani ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656989178","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656989178"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safari ilipoendelea joto lilikuwa jingi ndani ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656992087","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656992087"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliyafumba macho yangu nikinuia kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIYAFUMBA"," userResponse":" NILIYAFUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656992582","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656992581"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliyafumba macho yangu nikinuia kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHO"," userResponse":" MACHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656993067","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656993067"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliyafumba macho yangu nikinuia kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656994374","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656994374"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliyafumba macho yangu nikinuia kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIKINUIA"," userResponse":" NIKINUIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656995059","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656995059"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliyafumba macho yangu nikinuia kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULALA"," userResponse":" KULALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656998279","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656998278"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mawazo yangu yalirejea nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656998897","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656998896"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mawazo yangu yalirejea nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAWAZO"," userResponse":" MAWAZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548656999423","data":{"timestamp":" 1548656999422"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mawazo yangu yalirejea nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657000489","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657000489"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mawazo yangu yalirejea nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALIREJEA"," userResponse":" YALIREJEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657001402","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657001401"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mawazo yangu yalirejea nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657003675","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657003675"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je mamangu atakuwa salama?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657004874","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657004874"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je mamangu atakuwa salama?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMANGU"," userResponse":" MAMANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657005704","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657005703"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je mamangu atakuwa salama?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ATAKUWA"," userResponse":" ATAKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657006862","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657006861"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je mamangu atakuwa salama?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SALAMA"," userResponse":" SALAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657009201","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657009201"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je sungura wangu wataleta hela zozote?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657010087","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657010087"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je sungura wangu wataleta hela zozote?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657010846","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657010845"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je sungura wangu wataleta hela zozote?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657011886","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657011886"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je sungura wangu wataleta hela zozote?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATALETA"," userResponse":" WATALETA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657012311","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657012311"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je sungura wangu wataleta hela zozote?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HELA"," userResponse":" HELA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657013173","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657013171"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je sungura wangu wataleta hela zozote?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZOZOTE"," userResponse":" ZOZOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657015294","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657015293"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndugu yangu atakumbuka kunyunyizia maji miche ya miti yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657016201","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657016200"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndugu yangu atakumbuka kunyunyizia maji miche ya miti yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDUGU"," userResponse":" NDUGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657016635","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657016635"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndugu yangu atakumbuka kunyunyizia maji miche ya miti yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657017763","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657017763"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndugu yangu atakumbuka kunyunyizia maji miche ya miti yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ATAKUMBUKA"," userResponse":" ATAKUMBUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657018898","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657018897"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndugu yangu atakumbuka kunyunyizia maji miche ya miti yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNYUNYIZIA"," userResponse":" KUNYUNYIZIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657019376","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657019376"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndugu yangu atakumbuka kunyunyizia maji miche ya miti yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657020022","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657020022"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndugu yangu atakumbuka kunyunyizia maji miche ya miti yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MICHE"," userResponse":" MICHE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657020090","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657020090"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndugu yangu atakumbuka kunyunyizia maji miche ya miti yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657020608","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657020607"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndugu yangu atakumbuka kunyunyizia maji miche ya miti yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MITI"," userResponse":" MITI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657021174","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657021174"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndugu yangu atakumbuka kunyunyizia maji miche ya miti yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657024527","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657024526"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani nilikariri jina la mahali mjombangu aliishi katika jiji kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIANI"," userResponse":" NJIANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657025517","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657025515"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani nilikariri jina la mahali mjombangu aliishi katika jiji kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIKARIRI"," userResponse":" NILIKARIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657026363","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657026363"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani nilikariri jina la mahali mjombangu aliishi katika jiji kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JINA"," userResponse":" JINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657026635","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657026635"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani nilikariri jina la mahali mjombangu aliishi katika jiji kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657027432","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657027432"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani nilikariri jina la mahali mjombangu aliishi katika jiji kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHALI"," userResponse":" MAHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657028323","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657028322"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani nilikariri jina la mahali mjombangu aliishi katika jiji kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJOMBANGU"," userResponse":" MJOMBANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657029109","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657029108"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani nilikariri jina la mahali mjombangu aliishi katika jiji kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIISHI"," userResponse":" ALIISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657030067","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657030067"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani nilikariri jina la mahali mjombangu aliishi katika jiji kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657030510","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657030510"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani nilikariri jina la mahali mjombangu aliishi katika jiji kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIJI"," userResponse":" JIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657031045","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657031045"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani nilikariri jina la mahali mjombangu aliishi katika jiji kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657033615","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657033614"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa bado najisemea wakati nilipatwa na usingizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIKUWA"," userResponse":" NILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657034075","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657034074"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa bado najisemea wakati nilipatwa na usingizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BADO"," userResponse":" BADO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657035112","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657035111"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa bado najisemea wakati nilipatwa na usingizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAJISEMEA"," userResponse":" NAJISEMEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657035756","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657035756"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa bado najisemea wakati nilipatwa na usingizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657036573","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657036572"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa bado najisemea wakati nilipatwa na usingizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIPATWA"," userResponse":" NILIPATWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657036761","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657036761"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa bado najisemea wakati nilipatwa na usingizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657037558","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657037558"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa bado najisemea wakati nilipatwa na usingizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USINGIZI"," userResponse":" USINGIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657040433","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657040432"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya saa tisa niliamshwa kwa kelele za kuita abiria waliokwenda katika kijiji changu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADA"," userResponse":" BAADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657040673","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657040672"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya saa tisa niliamshwa kwa kelele za kuita abiria waliokwenda katika kijiji changu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657041018","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657041017"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya saa tisa niliamshwa kwa kelele za kuita abiria waliokwenda katika kijiji changu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAA"," userResponse":" SAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657041628","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657041628"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya saa tisa niliamshwa kwa kelele za kuita abiria waliokwenda katika kijiji changu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TISA"," userResponse":" TISA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657042842","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657042842"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya saa tisa niliamshwa kwa kelele za kuita abiria waliokwenda katika kijiji changu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIAMSHWA"," userResponse":" NILIAMSHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657043093","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657043093"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya saa tisa niliamshwa kwa kelele za kuita abiria waliokwenda katika kijiji changu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657043872","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657043871"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya saa tisa niliamshwa kwa kelele za kuita abiria waliokwenda katika kijiji changu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KELELE"," userResponse":" KELELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657044073","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657044073"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya saa tisa niliamshwa kwa kelele za kuita abiria waliokwenda katika kijiji changu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657044816","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657044816"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya saa tisa niliamshwa kwa kelele za kuita abiria waliokwenda katika kijiji changu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUITA"," userResponse":" KUITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657045587","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657045587"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya saa tisa niliamshwa kwa kelele za kuita abiria waliokwenda katika kijiji changu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ABIRIA"," userResponse":" ABIRIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657046773","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657046772"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya saa tisa niliamshwa kwa kelele za kuita abiria waliokwenda katika kijiji changu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIOKWENDA"," userResponse":" WALIOKWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657047395","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657047394"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya saa tisa niliamshwa kwa kelele za kuita abiria waliokwenda katika kijiji changu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657048049","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657048048"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya saa tisa niliamshwa kwa kelele za kuita abiria waliokwenda katika kijiji changu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" KIJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657048631","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657048631"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya saa tisa niliamshwa kwa kelele za kuita abiria waliokwenda katika kijiji changu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHANGU"," userResponse":" CHANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657051197","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657051196"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilichukuwa mfuko wangu mdogo na kuruka nje ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILICHUKUWA"," userResponse":" NILICHUKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657051677","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657051676"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilichukuwa mfuko wangu mdogo na kuruka nje ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFUKO"," userResponse":" MFUKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657052119","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657052118"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilichukuwa mfuko wangu mdogo na kuruka nje ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657052910","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657052910"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilichukuwa mfuko wangu mdogo na kuruka nje ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOGO"," userResponse":" MDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657053336","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657053335"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilichukuwa mfuko wangu mdogo na kuruka nje ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657054195","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657054195"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilichukuwa mfuko wangu mdogo na kuruka nje ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" KURUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657054769","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657054769"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilichukuwa mfuko wangu mdogo na kuruka nje ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJE"," userResponse":" NJE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657054849","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657054849"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilichukuwa mfuko wangu mdogo na kuruka nje ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657055305","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657055305"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilichukuwa mfuko wangu mdogo na kuruka nje ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657058285","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657058285"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kurudi lilikuwa linajaa upesi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657058385","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657058385"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kurudi lilikuwa linajaa upesi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657059262","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657059262"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kurudi lilikuwa linajaa upesi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUDI"," userResponse":" KURUDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657060163","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657060162"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kurudi lilikuwa linajaa upesi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIKUWA"," userResponse":" LILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657061033","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657061032"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kurudi lilikuwa linajaa upesi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LINAJAA"," userResponse":" LINAJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657061618","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657061617"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kurudi lilikuwa linajaa upesi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPESI"," userResponse":" UPESI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657063862","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657063861"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye lingeanza safari ya kwenda mashariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUDA"," userResponse":" MUDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657064475","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657064474"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye lingeanza safari ya kwenda mashariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFUPI"," userResponse":" MFUPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657065127","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657065127"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye lingeanza safari ya kwenda mashariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADAYE"," userResponse":" BAADAYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657066014","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657066014"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye lingeanza safari ya kwenda mashariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LINGEANZA"," userResponse":" LINGEANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657067000","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657067000"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye lingeanza safari ya kwenda mashariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAFARI"," userResponse":" SAFARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657067109","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657067108"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye lingeanza safari ya kwenda mashariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657067564","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657067563"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye lingeanza safari ya kwenda mashariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657068505","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657068504"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye lingeanza safari ya kwenda mashariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHARIKI"," userResponse":" MASHARIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657070997","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657070996"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jambo la maana kwangu wakati huo lilikuwa kuanza kutafuta nyumba ya mjombangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JAMBO"," userResponse":" JAMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657071134","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657071133"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jambo la maana kwangu wakati huo lilikuwa kuanza kutafuta nyumba ya mjombangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657071788","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657071788"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jambo la maana kwangu wakati huo lilikuwa kuanza kutafuta nyumba ya mjombangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAANA"," userResponse":" MAANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657072311","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657072310"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jambo la maana kwangu wakati huo lilikuwa kuanza kutafuta nyumba ya mjombangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANGU"," userResponse":" KWANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657072994","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657072994"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jambo la maana kwangu wakati huo lilikuwa kuanza kutafuta nyumba ya mjombangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657073835","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657073835"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jambo la maana kwangu wakati huo lilikuwa kuanza kutafuta nyumba ya mjombangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" HUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657074402","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657074400"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jambo la maana kwangu wakati huo lilikuwa kuanza kutafuta nyumba ya mjombangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIKUWA"," userResponse":" LILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657075040","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657075040"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jambo la maana kwangu wakati huo lilikuwa kuanza kutafuta nyumba ya mjombangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUANZA"," userResponse":" KUANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657075931","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657075931"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jambo la maana kwangu wakati huo lilikuwa kuanza kutafuta nyumba ya mjombangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTAFUTA"," userResponse":" KUTAFUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657076761","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657076760"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jambo la maana kwangu wakati huo lilikuwa kuanza kutafuta nyumba ya mjombangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657076998","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657076997"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jambo la maana kwangu wakati huo lilikuwa kuanza kutafuta nyumba ya mjombangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657077893","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657077893"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jambo la maana kwangu wakati huo lilikuwa kuanza kutafuta nyumba ya mjombangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJOMBANGU"," userResponse":" MJOMBANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657080462","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657080460"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Jambo la maana kwangu wakati huo lilikuwa kuanza kutafuta nyumba ya mjombangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657080561","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657080561"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3d2a2018-e3fa-4a0b-8813-cb328654b3aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jambo la maana kwangu wakati huo lilikuwa kuanza kutafuta nyumba ya mjombangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJOMBANGU"," userResponse":" MJOMBANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657089544","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657089544"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" ce670cfa-5b5a-43f2-8e98-09eefca78ad2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-f-n"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657092922","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657092922"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" ce670cfa-5b5a-43f2-8e98-09eefca78ad2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_t-n-b"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657096247","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657096246"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" ce670cfa-5b5a-43f2-8e98-09eefca78ad2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_d-s-ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657099364","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657099364"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" ce670cfa-5b5a-43f2-8e98-09eefca78ad2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_p-d-e"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657103283","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657103283"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" ce670cfa-5b5a-43f2-8e98-09eefca78ad2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_w-y-e"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657107449","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657107449"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" ce670cfa-5b5a-43f2-8e98-09eefca78ad2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_f-d-j"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657111503","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657111502"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" ce670cfa-5b5a-43f2-8e98-09eefca78ad2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_z-i-g"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657117039","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657117039"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" ce670cfa-5b5a-43f2-8e98-09eefca78ad2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_h_g-n-h"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657122886","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657122885"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" ce670cfa-5b5a-43f2-8e98-09eefca78ad2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_i-ch-r"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657131645","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657131645"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" ce670cfa-5b5a-43f2-8e98-09eefca78ad2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_j-h-t"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657135280","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657135280"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" ce670cfa-5b5a-43f2-8e98-09eefca78ad2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_j-k-o"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657141495","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657141495"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" ce670cfa-5b5a-43f2-8e98-09eefca78ad2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_l_w-l-f"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657144354","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657144354"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" ce670cfa-5b5a-43f2-8e98-09eefca78ad2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_m-n-s"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657148018","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657148018"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" ce670cfa-5b5a-43f2-8e98-09eefca78ad2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_b-h-n"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657151421","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657151421"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" ce670cfa-5b5a-43f2-8e98-09eefca78ad2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_w-o-y"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657154798","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657154798"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" ce670cfa-5b5a-43f2-8e98-09eefca78ad2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_p_m-p-s"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657158691","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657158691"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" ce670cfa-5b5a-43f2-8e98-09eefca78ad2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_r_v-r-d"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657162642","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657162642"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" ce670cfa-5b5a-43f2-8e98-09eefca78ad2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_s_i-h-s"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657167314","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657167314"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" ce670cfa-5b5a-43f2-8e98-09eefca78ad2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_t_t-r-z"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657172260","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657172260"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" ce670cfa-5b5a-43f2-8e98-09eefca78ad2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_u_u-i-h"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657175090","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657175089"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" ce670cfa-5b5a-43f2-8e98-09eefca78ad2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_v_v-i-k"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657179513","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657179512"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" ce670cfa-5b5a-43f2-8e98-09eefca78ad2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_w_d-w-m"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657182651","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657182651"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" ce670cfa-5b5a-43f2-8e98-09eefca78ad2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_y_n-y-f"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657185858","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657185857"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" ce670cfa-5b5a-43f2-8e98-09eefca78ad2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-j-h"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657191606","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657191606"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" ce670cfa-5b5a-43f2-8e98-09eefca78ad2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-j-h"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..20.off2.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657196806","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657196806"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" ce670cfa-5b5a-43f2-8e98-09eefca78ad2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-j-h"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657203317","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657203317"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" ce670cfa-5b5a-43f2-8e98-09eefca78ad2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-j-h"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657213772","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657213772"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani palikuwa na Bweha mvivu pia mjinga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657214639","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657214638"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani palikuwa na Bweha mvivu pia mjinga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657215354","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657215354"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani palikuwa na Bweha mvivu pia mjinga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIKUWA"," userResponse":" PALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657215568","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657215567"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani palikuwa na Bweha mvivu pia mjinga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657216137","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657216136"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani palikuwa na Bweha mvivu pia mjinga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWEHA"," userResponse":" BWEHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657216955","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657216955"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani palikuwa na Bweha mvivu pia mjinga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MVIVU"," userResponse":" MVIVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657217340","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657217340"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani palikuwa na Bweha mvivu pia mjinga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PIA"," userResponse":" PIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657218018","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657218018"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani palikuwa na Bweha mvivu pia mjinga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJINGA"," userResponse":" MJINGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657220584","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657220583"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliishi na babake mzee katika kichaka cha Kalahari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIISHI"," userResponse":" ALIISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657220786","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657220786"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliishi na babake mzee katika kichaka cha Kalahari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657221443","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657221442"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliishi na babake mzee katika kichaka cha Kalahari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABAKE"," userResponse":" BABAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657222098","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657222098"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliishi na babake mzee katika kichaka cha Kalahari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MZEE"," userResponse":" MZEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657222738","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657222738"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliishi na babake mzee katika kichaka cha Kalahari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657223343","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657223343"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliishi na babake mzee katika kichaka cha Kalahari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHAKA"," userResponse":" KICHAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657223572","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657223572"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliishi na babake mzee katika kichaka cha Kalahari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657224480","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657224480"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliishi na babake mzee katika kichaka cha Kalahari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALAHARI"," userResponse":" KALAHARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657227715","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657227715"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Asubuhi moja Bweha Mzee aliamka na kumpata mwanawe amelala juani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASUBUHI"," userResponse":" ASUBUHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657228349","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657228348"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Asubuhi moja Bweha Mzee aliamka na kumpata mwanawe amelala juani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657229151","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657229150"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Asubuhi moja Bweha Mzee aliamka na kumpata mwanawe amelala juani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWEHA"," userResponse":" BWEHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657229788","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657229787"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Asubuhi moja Bweha Mzee aliamka na kumpata mwanawe amelala juani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MZEE"," userResponse":" MZEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657230813","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657230812"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Asubuhi moja Bweha Mzee aliamka na kumpata mwanawe amelala juani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIAMKA"," userResponse":" ALIAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657231316","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657231316"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Asubuhi moja Bweha Mzee aliamka na kumpata mwanawe amelala juani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657232184","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657232183"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Asubuhi moja Bweha Mzee aliamka na kumpata mwanawe amelala juani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMPATA"," userResponse":" KUMPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657232969","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657232969"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Asubuhi moja Bweha Mzee aliamka na kumpata mwanawe amelala juani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAWE"," userResponse":" MWANAWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657233703","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657233703"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Asubuhi moja Bweha Mzee aliamka na kumpata mwanawe amelala juani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMELALA"," userResponse":" AMELALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657234457","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657234457"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Asubuhi moja Bweha Mzee aliamka na kumpata mwanawe amelala juani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUANI"," userResponse":" JUANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657236898","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657236898"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nenda ukamtafute mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657237785","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657237784"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nenda ukamtafute mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKIKUWA"," userResponse":" HAKIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657238656","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657238655"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nenda ukamtafute mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAYARI"," userResponse":" TAYARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657239027","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657239027"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nenda ukamtafute mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657239512","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657239511"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nenda ukamtafute mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUZI"," userResponse":" MBUZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657240223","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657240222"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nenda ukamtafute mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657240673","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657240672"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nenda ukamtafute mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BADO"," userResponse":" BADO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657241418","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657241417"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nenda ukamtafute mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIZINI"," userResponse":" ZIZINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657243796","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657243796"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nenda ukamtafute mke."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WEWE"," userResponse":" WEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657244564","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657244564"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nenda ukamtafute mke."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJANA"," userResponse":" KIJANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657245119","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657245119"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nenda ukamtafute mke."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657245637","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657245636"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nenda ukamtafute mke."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MVIVU"," userResponse":" MVIVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657246159","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657246158"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nenda ukamtafute mke."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657248599","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657248598"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nenda ukamtafute mke."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NENDA"," userResponse":" NENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657249712","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657249711"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nenda ukamtafute mke."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKAMTAFUTE"," userResponse":" UKAMTAFUTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657250035","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657250035"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nenda ukamtafute mke."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKE"," userResponse":" MKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657253013","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657253012"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimezeeka sana siwezi kukukimu tena babake Bweha alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIMEZEEKA"," userResponse":" NIMEZEEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657253566","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657253566"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimezeeka sana siwezi kukukimu tena babake Bweha alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657254200","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657254200"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimezeeka sana siwezi kukukimu tena babake Bweha alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIWEZI"," userResponse":" SIWEZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657255133","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657255133"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimezeeka sana siwezi kukukimu tena babake Bweha alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKUKIMU"," userResponse":" KUKUKIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657255593","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657255592"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimezeeka sana siwezi kukukimu tena babake Bweha alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657256766","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657256766"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimezeeka sana siwezi kukukimu tena babake Bweha alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABAKE"," userResponse":" BABAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657257220","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657257220"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimezeeka sana siwezi kukukimu tena babake Bweha alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWEHA"," userResponse":" BWEHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657258072","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657258071"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimezeeka sana siwezi kukukimu tena babake Bweha alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657260087","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657260087"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha aliruka juu na kuwapeleka mbuzi malishoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657260806","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657260806"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha aliruka juu na kuwapeleka mbuzi malishoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657261452","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657261452"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha aliruka juu na kuwapeleka mbuzi malishoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWEHA"," userResponse":" BWEHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657262274","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657262274"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha aliruka juu na kuwapeleka mbuzi malishoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIRUKA"," userResponse":" ALIRUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657262874","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657262873"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha aliruka juu na kuwapeleka mbuzi malishoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657263072","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657263071"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha aliruka juu na kuwapeleka mbuzi malishoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657264009","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657264009"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha aliruka juu na kuwapeleka mbuzi malishoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWAPELEKA"," userResponse":" KUWAPELEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657264451","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657264451"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha aliruka juu na kuwapeleka mbuzi malishoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUZI"," userResponse":" MBUZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657265336","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657265336"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha aliruka juu na kuwapeleka mbuzi malishoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MALISHONI"," userResponse":" MALISHONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657268824","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657268823"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kichakani aliona kitu kilichoangaza juu ya mwamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHAKANI"," userResponse":" KICHAKANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657269699","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657269698"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kichakani aliona kitu kilichoangaza juu ya mwamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIONA"," userResponse":" ALIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657270190","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657270190"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kichakani aliona kitu kilichoangaza juu ya mwamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITU"," userResponse":" KITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657271449","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657271447"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kichakani aliona kitu kilichoangaza juu ya mwamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILICHOANGAZA"," userResponse":" KILICHOANGAZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657272003","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657272003"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kichakani aliona kitu kilichoangaza juu ya mwamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657272151","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657272151"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kichakani aliona kitu kilichoangaza juu ya mwamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657272697","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657272697"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kichakani aliona kitu kilichoangaza juu ya mwamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWAMBA"," userResponse":" MWAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657275321","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657275320"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alizidi kuukaribia mwamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIZIDI"," userResponse":" ALIZIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657276448","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657276448"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alizidi kuukaribia mwamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUUKARIBIA"," userResponse":" KUUKARIBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657276994","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657276993"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alizidi kuukaribia mwamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWAMBA"," userResponse":" MWAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657279850","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657279849"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipozidi kuukaribia ndipo mwangaza ulipozidi kupendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOZIDI"," userResponse":" ALIPOZIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657281086","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657281085"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipozidi kuukaribia ndipo mwangaza ulipozidi kupendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUUKARIBIA"," userResponse":" KUUKARIBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657281841","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657281840"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipozidi kuukaribia ndipo mwangaza ulipozidi kupendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIPO"," userResponse":" NDIPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657282515","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657282515"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipozidi kuukaribia ndipo mwangaza ulipozidi kupendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANGAZA"," userResponse":" MWANGAZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657283357","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657283356"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipozidi kuukaribia ndipo mwangaza ulipozidi kupendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIPOZIDI"," userResponse":" ULIPOZIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657284212","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657284211"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipozidi kuukaribia ndipo mwangaza ulipozidi kupendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPENDEZA"," userResponse":" KUPENDEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657286724","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657286723"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda huyu ndiye mke wake?!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LABDA"," userResponse":" LABDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657287220","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657287219"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda huyu ndiye mke wake?!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYU"," userResponse":" HUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657287749","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657287749"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda huyu ndiye mke wake?!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIYE"," userResponse":" NDIYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657288258","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657288257"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda huyu ndiye mke wake?!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKE"," userResponse":" MKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657288904","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657288903"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda huyu ndiye mke wake?!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657292257","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657292257"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U-mzuri mno Bweha aliueleza mng'aro."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657292277","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657292277"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U-mzuri mno Bweha aliueleza mng'aro."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MZURI"," userResponse":" MZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657292750","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657292749"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U-mzuri mno Bweha aliueleza mng'aro."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MNO"," userResponse":" MNO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657293527","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657293526"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U-mzuri mno Bweha aliueleza mng'aro."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWEHA"," userResponse":" BWEHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657294506","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657294506"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U-mzuri mno Bweha aliueleza mng'aro."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIUELEZA"," userResponse":" ALIUELEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657295163","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657295163"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U-mzuri mno Bweha aliueleza mng'aro."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MNG"," userResponse":" MNG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657295183","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657295182"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U-mzuri mno Bweha aliueleza mng'aro."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ARO"," userResponse":" ARO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657297883","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657297883"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbona uko peke yako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657298205","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657298205"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbona uko peke yako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WEWE"," userResponse":" WEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657298379","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657298378"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbona uko peke yako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657299271","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657299270"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbona uko peke yako?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657301710","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657301710"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbona uko peke yako?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBONA"," userResponse":" MBONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657301961","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657301961"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbona uko peke yako?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKO"," userResponse":" UKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657302848","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657302847"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbona uko peke yako?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PEKE"," userResponse":" PEKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657303355","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657303354"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbona uko peke yako?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKO"," userResponse":" YAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657305689","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657305689"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia yangu waliniacha hapa wakati walihama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657305927","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657305927"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia yangu waliniacha hapa wakati walihama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657306370","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657306370"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia yangu waliniacha hapa wakati walihama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" JUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657307046","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657307045"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia yangu waliniacha hapa wakati walihama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MNG"," userResponse":" MNG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657307069","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657307069"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia yangu waliniacha hapa wakati walihama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ARO"," userResponse":" ARO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657307898","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657307897"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia yangu waliniacha hapa wakati walihama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIJIBU"," userResponse":" ULIJIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657310349","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657310349"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia yangu waliniacha hapa wakati walihama."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" FAMILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657310974","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657310974"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia yangu waliniacha hapa wakati walihama."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657312210","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657312210"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia yangu waliniacha hapa wakati walihama."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALINIACHA"," userResponse":" WALINIACHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657312767","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657312766"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia yangu waliniacha hapa wakati walihama."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPA"," userResponse":" HAPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657313623","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657313623"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia yangu waliniacha hapa wakati walihama."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657314430","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657314430"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia yangu waliniacha hapa wakati walihama."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIHAMA"," userResponse":" WALIHAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657317388","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657317387"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawakutaka kunibeba maanake mimi ni moto sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWAKUTAKA"," userResponse":" HAWAKUTAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657318355","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657318354"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawakutaka kunibeba maanake mimi ni moto sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNIBEBA"," userResponse":" KUNIBEBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657319270","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657319269"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawakutaka kunibeba maanake mimi ni moto sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAANAKE"," userResponse":" MAANAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657319695","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657319694"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawakutaka kunibeba maanake mimi ni moto sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657319880","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657319879"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawakutaka kunibeba maanake mimi ni moto sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657320313","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657320313"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawakutaka kunibeba maanake mimi ni moto sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOTO"," userResponse":" MOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657320817","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657320817"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawakutaka kunibeba maanake mimi ni moto sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657323778","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657323778"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bweha alisema Lakini wewe u-mzuri sana!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWEHA"," userResponse":" BWEHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657324636","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657324636"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bweha alisema Lakini wewe u-mzuri sana!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657325436","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657325436"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bweha alisema Lakini wewe u-mzuri sana!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657325841","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657325841"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bweha alisema Lakini wewe u-mzuri sana!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WEWE"," userResponse":" WEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657326737","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657326737"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bweha alisema Lakini wewe u-mzuri sana!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657326766","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657326765"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bweha alisema Lakini wewe u-mzuri sana!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MZURI"," userResponse":" MZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657327560","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657327560"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bweha alisema Lakini wewe u-mzuri sana!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657329881","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657329881"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakupeleka nyumbani nikujulishe kwa babangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657330937","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657330937"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakupeleka nyumbani nikujulishe kwa babangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITAKUBEBA"," userResponse":" NITAKUBEBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657334099","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657334099"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakupeleka nyumbani nikujulishe kwa babangu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITAKUPELEKA"," userResponse":" NITAKUPELEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657334997","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657334997"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakupeleka nyumbani nikujulishe kwa babangu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657335985","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657335984"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakupeleka nyumbani nikujulishe kwa babangu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIKUJULISHE"," userResponse":" NIKUJULISHE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657336304","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657336303"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakupeleka nyumbani nikujulishe kwa babangu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657337073","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657337073"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakupeleka nyumbani nikujulishe kwa babangu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABANGU"," userResponse":" BABANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657339693","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657339692"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini usilalamike nikiwa moto kuliko unavyoweza kuhimili jua lilisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAWA"," userResponse":" SAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657340555","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657340555"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini usilalamike nikiwa moto kuliko unavyoweza kuhimili jua lilisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNAWEZA"," userResponse":" UNAWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657341362","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657341362"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini usilalamike nikiwa moto kuliko unavyoweza kuhimili jua lilisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIBEBA"," userResponse":" NIBEBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657344181","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657344180"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini usilalamike nikiwa moto kuliko unavyoweza kuhimili jua lilisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657345422","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657345422"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini usilalamike nikiwa moto kuliko unavyoweza kuhimili jua lilisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USILALAMIKE"," userResponse":" USILALAMIKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657345937","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657345937"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini usilalamike nikiwa moto kuliko unavyoweza kuhimili jua lilisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIKIWA"," userResponse":" NIKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657346257","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657346256"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini usilalamike nikiwa moto kuliko unavyoweza kuhimili jua lilisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOTO"," userResponse":" MOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657346956","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657346956"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini usilalamike nikiwa moto kuliko unavyoweza kuhimili jua lilisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKO"," userResponse":" KULIKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657347823","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657347823"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini usilalamike nikiwa moto kuliko unavyoweza kuhimili jua lilisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNAVYOWEZA"," userResponse":" UNAVYOWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657348760","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657348760"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini usilalamike nikiwa moto kuliko unavyoweza kuhimili jua lilisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUHIMILI"," userResponse":" KUHIMILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657349426","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657349426"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini usilalamike nikiwa moto kuliko unavyoweza kuhimili jua lilisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" JUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657350320","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657350319"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini usilalamike nikiwa moto kuliko unavyoweza kuhimili jua lilisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILISEMA"," userResponse":" LILISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657352761","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657352761"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657353433","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657353433"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657354155","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657354154"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWEHA"," userResponse":" BWEHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657354780","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657354779"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIENDA"," userResponse":" ALIENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657355467","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657355464"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657355841","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657355841"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" BILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657356464","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657356464"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGOZI"," userResponse":" NGOZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657357051","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657357051"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALA"," userResponse":" WALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657357643","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657357642"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYOYA"," userResponse":" MANYOYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657358592","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657358592"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGONGONI"," userResponse":" MGONGONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657359261","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657359260"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657359715","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657359715"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657360399","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657360398"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" BILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657360829","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657360828"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKE"," userResponse":" MKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657363580","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657363579"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake aliuguza mgongo wa Bweha kwa kutumia mafuta maalumu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABAKE"," userResponse":" BABAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657364413","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657364412"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake aliuguza mgongo wa Bweha kwa kutumia mafuta maalumu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIUGUZA"," userResponse":" ALIUGUZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657364982","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657364981"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake aliuguza mgongo wa Bweha kwa kutumia mafuta maalumu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGONGO"," userResponse":" MGONGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657365183","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657365183"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake aliuguza mgongo wa Bweha kwa kutumia mafuta maalumu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657365665","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657365665"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake aliuguza mgongo wa Bweha kwa kutumia mafuta maalumu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWEHA"," userResponse":" BWEHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657366204","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657366203"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake aliuguza mgongo wa Bweha kwa kutumia mafuta maalumu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657366914","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657366914"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake aliuguza mgongo wa Bweha kwa kutumia mafuta maalumu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTUMIA"," userResponse":" KUTUMIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657367500","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657367499"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake aliuguza mgongo wa Bweha kwa kutumia mafuta maalumu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAFUTA"," userResponse":" MAFUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657368270","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657368270"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake aliuguza mgongo wa Bweha kwa kutumia mafuta maalumu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAALUMU"," userResponse":" MAALUMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657370183","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657370183"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na manyoya yakamea mara nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657370873","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657370873"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na manyoya yakamea mara nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYOYA"," userResponse":" MANYOYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657371607","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657371606"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na manyoya yakamea mara nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKAMEA"," userResponse":" YAKAMEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657371995","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657371995"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na manyoya yakamea mara nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657372690","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657372689"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na manyoya yakamea mara nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGINE"," userResponse":" NYINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657375362","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657375362"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657376034","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657376034"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657376759","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657376759"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWEHA"," userResponse":" BWEHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657377382","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657377382"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIENDA"," userResponse":" ALIENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657378069","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657378069"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657378458","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657378457"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" BILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657379081","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657379081"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGOZI"," userResponse":" NGOZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657379655","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657379655"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALA"," userResponse":" WALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657380229","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657380229"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYOYA"," userResponse":" MANYOYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657381163","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657381163"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGONGONI"," userResponse":" MGONGONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657381816","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657381816"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657382271","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657382271"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657382972","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657382972"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" BILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657383407","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657383407"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Bweha alienda nyumbani bila ngozi wala manyoya mgongoni vile vile bila mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKE"," userResponse":" MKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657386172","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657386172"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake aliuguza mgongo wa Bweha kwa kutumia mafuta maalumu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABAKE"," userResponse":" BABAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657387005","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657387004"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake aliuguza mgongo wa Bweha kwa kutumia mafuta maalumu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIUGUZA"," userResponse":" ALIUGUZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657387572","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657387572"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake aliuguza mgongo wa Bweha kwa kutumia mafuta maalumu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGONGO"," userResponse":" MGONGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657387771","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657387770"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake aliuguza mgongo wa Bweha kwa kutumia mafuta maalumu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657388254","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657388253"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake aliuguza mgongo wa Bweha kwa kutumia mafuta maalumu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWEHA"," userResponse":" BWEHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657388787","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657388787"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake aliuguza mgongo wa Bweha kwa kutumia mafuta maalumu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657389496","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657389496"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake aliuguza mgongo wa Bweha kwa kutumia mafuta maalumu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTUMIA"," userResponse":" KUTUMIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657390082","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657390082"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake aliuguza mgongo wa Bweha kwa kutumia mafuta maalumu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAFUTA"," userResponse":" MAFUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657390851","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657390850"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babake aliuguza mgongo wa Bweha kwa kutumia mafuta maalumu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAALUMU"," userResponse":" MAALUMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657393359","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657393359"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na manyoya yakamea mara nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657394055","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657394054"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na manyoya yakamea mara nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYOYA"," userResponse":" MANYOYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657394786","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657394786"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na manyoya yakamea mara nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKAMEA"," userResponse":" YAKAMEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657395176","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657395176"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na manyoya yakamea mara nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657395859","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657395859"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na manyoya yakamea mara nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGINE"," userResponse":" NYINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657399283","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657399282"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini manyoya mapya yalikuwa rangi tofauti na yale mengine mwilini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657399887","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657399887"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini manyoya mapya yalikuwa rangi tofauti na yale mengine mwilini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYOYA"," userResponse":" MANYOYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657400419","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657400419"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini manyoya mapya yalikuwa rangi tofauti na yale mengine mwilini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAPYA"," userResponse":" MAPYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657401116","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657401115"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini manyoya mapya yalikuwa rangi tofauti na yale mengine mwilini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALIKUWA"," userResponse":" YALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657401539","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657401539"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini manyoya mapya yalikuwa rangi tofauti na yale mengine mwilini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657402298","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657402297"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini manyoya mapya yalikuwa rangi tofauti na yale mengine mwilini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOFAUTI"," userResponse":" TOFAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657402497","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657402497"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini manyoya mapya yalikuwa rangi tofauti na yale mengine mwilini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657402851","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657402851"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini manyoya mapya yalikuwa rangi tofauti na yale mengine mwilini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALE"," userResponse":" YALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657403444","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657403444"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini manyoya mapya yalikuwa rangi tofauti na yale mengine mwilini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENGINE"," userResponse":" MENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657404248","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657404248"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini manyoya mapya yalikuwa rangi tofauti na yale mengine mwilini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWILINI"," userResponse":" MWILINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657406560","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657406560"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi zote tofauti zilimkumbusha Bweha kila mara kutokuwa mjinga tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657407131","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657407131"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi zote tofauti zilimkumbusha Bweha kila mara kutokuwa mjinga tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZOTE"," userResponse":" ZOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657407931","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657407931"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi zote tofauti zilimkumbusha Bweha kila mara kutokuwa mjinga tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOFAUTI"," userResponse":" TOFAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657409024","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657409024"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi zote tofauti zilimkumbusha Bweha kila mara kutokuwa mjinga tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZILIMKUMBUSHA"," userResponse":" ZILIMKUMBUSHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657409594","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657409593"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi zote tofauti zilimkumbusha Bweha kila mara kutokuwa mjinga tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWEHA"," userResponse":" BWEHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657410293","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657410293"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi zote tofauti zilimkumbusha Bweha kila mara kutokuwa mjinga tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657410878","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657410878"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi zote tofauti zilimkumbusha Bweha kila mara kutokuwa mjinga tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657411936","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657411936"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi zote tofauti zilimkumbusha Bweha kila mara kutokuwa mjinga tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKUWA"," userResponse":" KUTOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657412653","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657412653"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi zote tofauti zilimkumbusha Bweha kila mara kutokuwa mjinga tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJINGA"," userResponse":" MJINGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657413146","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657413146"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi zote tofauti zilimkumbusha Bweha kila mara kutokuwa mjinga tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657430121","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657430120"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Rangi zote tofauti zilimkumbusha Bweha kila mara kutokuwa mjinga tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657430204","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657430204"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" cfebc75c-768e-440b-8e77-9873572efb89"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi zote tofauti zilimkumbusha Bweha kila mara kutokuwa mjinga tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657439667","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657439667"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" da3d2611-a392-4831-b867-0b7c79741bfb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657441002","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657441002"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" da3d2611-a392-4831-b867-0b7c79741bfb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657441069","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657441069"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" da3d2611-a392-4831-b867-0b7c79741bfb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657448833","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657448833"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" da3d2611-a392-4831-b867-0b7c79741bfb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:N..N.all.rand.all.stat.show.104","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657456066","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657456066"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" da3d2611-a392-4831-b867-0b7c79741bfb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_38"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657465588","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657465588"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale wasichana watatu walienda kutafuta kuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657466281","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657466281"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale wasichana watatu walienda kutafuta kuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657466504","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657466504"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale wasichana watatu walienda kutafuta kuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657467224","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657467223"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale wasichana watatu walienda kutafuta kuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657468536","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657468535"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale wasichana watatu walienda kutafuta kuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WASICHANA"," userResponse":" WASICHANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657469194","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657469194"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale wasichana watatu walienda kutafuta kuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATATU"," userResponse":" WATATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657470085","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657470085"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale wasichana watatu walienda kutafuta kuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIENDA"," userResponse":" WALIENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657471004","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657471004"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale wasichana watatu walienda kutafuta kuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTAFUTA"," userResponse":" KUTAFUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657471714","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657471714"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale wasichana watatu walienda kutafuta kuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNI"," userResponse":" KUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657474942","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657474942"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa siku yenye joto kwa hivyo walienda mtoni kuogelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657475542","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657475541"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa siku yenye joto kwa hivyo walienda mtoni kuogelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657476054","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657476054"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa siku yenye joto kwa hivyo walienda mtoni kuogelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YENYE"," userResponse":" YENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657476783","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657476783"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa siku yenye joto kwa hivyo walienda mtoni kuogelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JOTO"," userResponse":" JOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657477645","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657477644"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa siku yenye joto kwa hivyo walienda mtoni kuogelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657478057","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657478057"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa siku yenye joto kwa hivyo walienda mtoni kuogelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657478851","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657478851"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa siku yenye joto kwa hivyo walienda mtoni kuogelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIENDA"," userResponse":" WALIENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657479504","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657479504"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa siku yenye joto kwa hivyo walienda mtoni kuogelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTONI"," userResponse":" MTONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657480498","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657480498"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa siku yenye joto kwa hivyo walienda mtoni kuogelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUOGELEA"," userResponse":" KUOGELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657483505","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657483505"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walicheza wakirushiania maji na kuogelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALICHEZA"," userResponse":" WALICHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657485377","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657485377"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walicheza wakirushiania maji na kuogelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIRUSHIANIA"," userResponse":" WAKIRUSHIANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657486041","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657486040"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walicheza wakirushiania maji na kuogelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657486244","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657486244"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walicheza wakirushiania maji na kuogelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657487307","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657487307"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walicheza wakirushiania maji na kuogelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUOGELEA"," userResponse":" KUOGELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657490448","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657490447"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ghafla waligundua kuwa saa zilikuwa zimeenda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GHAFLA"," userResponse":" GHAFLA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657491847","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657491846"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ghafla waligundua kuwa saa zilikuwa zimeenda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIGUNDUA"," userResponse":" WALIGUNDUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657492298","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657492297"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ghafla waligundua kuwa saa zilikuwa zimeenda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657492760","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657492760"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ghafla waligundua kuwa saa zilikuwa zimeenda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAA"," userResponse":" SAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657493578","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657493577"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ghafla waligundua kuwa saa zilikuwa zimeenda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ZILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657494817","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657494816"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ghafla waligundua kuwa saa zilikuwa zimeenda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIMEENDA"," userResponse":" ZIMEENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657498265","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657498264"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliharakisha kurudi kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIHARAKISHA"," userResponse":" WALIHARAKISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657498979","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657498979"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliharakisha kurudi kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUDI"," userResponse":" KURUDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657500111","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657500111"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliharakisha kurudi kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJINI"," userResponse":" KIJIJINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657503834","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657503834"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa karibu nyumbani Nozibele aliweka mkono wake shingoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIPOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657504556","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657504556"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa karibu nyumbani Nozibele aliweka mkono wake shingoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" KARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657505518","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657505518"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa karibu nyumbani Nozibele aliweka mkono wake shingoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657506593","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657506592"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa karibu nyumbani Nozibele aliweka mkono wake shingoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NOZIBELE"," userResponse":" NOZIBELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657507588","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657507587"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa karibu nyumbani Nozibele aliweka mkono wake shingoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWEKA"," userResponse":" ALIWEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657508290","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657508290"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa karibu nyumbani Nozibele aliweka mkono wake shingoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKONO"," userResponse":" MKONO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657508717","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657508716"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa karibu nyumbani Nozibele aliweka mkono wake shingoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657509570","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657509569"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokuwa karibu nyumbani Nozibele aliweka mkono wake shingoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHINGONI"," userResponse":" SHINGONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657512309","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657512309"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amesahau mkufu wake!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657513564","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657513563"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amesahau mkufu wake!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMESAHAU"," userResponse":" AMESAHAU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657514548","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657514548"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amesahau mkufu wake!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUFU"," userResponse":" MKUFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657515039","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657515038"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amesahau mkufu wake!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657517981","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657517981"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" aliwasihi marafiki zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAFADHALI"," userResponse":" TAFADHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657518679","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657518678"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" aliwasihi marafiki zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RUDINI"," userResponse":" RUDINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657519634","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657519634"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" aliwasihi marafiki zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAMI"," userResponse":" NAMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657522770","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657522770"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" aliwasihi marafiki zake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWASIHI"," userResponse":" ALIWASIHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657523597","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657523597"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" aliwasihi marafiki zake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARAFIKI"," userResponse":" MARAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657524211","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657524210"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" aliwasihi marafiki zake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657526986","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657526985"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini marafiki zake walisema kwamba saa zilikuwa zimeenda sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657528110","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657528109"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini marafiki zake walisema kwamba saa zilikuwa zimeenda sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARAFIKI"," userResponse":" MARAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657528638","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657528638"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini marafiki zake walisema kwamba saa zilikuwa zimeenda sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657529505","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657529504"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini marafiki zake walisema kwamba saa zilikuwa zimeenda sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALISEMA"," userResponse":" WALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657530092","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657530092"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini marafiki zake walisema kwamba saa zilikuwa zimeenda sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" KWAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657530668","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657530667"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini marafiki zake walisema kwamba saa zilikuwa zimeenda sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAA"," userResponse":" SAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657531533","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657531533"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini marafiki zake walisema kwamba saa zilikuwa zimeenda sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ZILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657532663","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657532662"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini marafiki zake walisema kwamba saa zilikuwa zimeenda sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIMEENDA"," userResponse":" ZIMEENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657533636","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657533635"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini marafiki zake walisema kwamba saa zilikuwa zimeenda sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657536315","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657536315"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Nozibele alirudi mtoni peke yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657536890","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657536890"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Nozibele alirudi mtoni peke yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657537755","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657537755"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Nozibele alirudi mtoni peke yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NOZIBELE"," userResponse":" NOZIBELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657538890","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657538889"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Nozibele alirudi mtoni peke yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIRUDI"," userResponse":" ALIRUDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657539602","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657539601"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Nozibele alirudi mtoni peke yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTONI"," userResponse":" MTONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657540414","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657540414"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Nozibele alirudi mtoni peke yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PEKE"," userResponse":" PEKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657540690","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657540690"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo Nozibele alirudi mtoni peke yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657543652","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657543651"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliupata mkufu wake na kuharakisha kurudi nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIUPATA"," userResponse":" ALIUPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657544086","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657544085"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliupata mkufu wake na kuharakisha kurudi nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUFU"," userResponse":" MKUFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657545121","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657545121"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliupata mkufu wake na kuharakisha kurudi nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657545730","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657545729"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliupata mkufu wake na kuharakisha kurudi nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657546946","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657546946"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliupata mkufu wake na kuharakisha kurudi nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUHARAKISHA"," userResponse":" KUHARAKISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657547702","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657547701"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliupata mkufu wake na kuharakisha kurudi nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUDI"," userResponse":" KURUDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657548630","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657548626"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliupata mkufu wake na kuharakisha kurudi nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657551565","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657551564"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alipotea gizani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657552883","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657552882"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alipotea gizani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOTEA"," userResponse":" ALIPOTEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657553807","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657553807"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini alipotea gizani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GIZANI"," userResponse":" GIZANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657556735","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657556734"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa umbali aliona mwangaza ukitokezea chumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657557986","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657557986"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa umbali aliona mwangaza ukitokezea chumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMBALI"," userResponse":" UMBALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657559189","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657559189"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa umbali aliona mwangaza ukitokezea chumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIONA"," userResponse":" ALIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657560342","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657560342"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa umbali aliona mwangaza ukitokezea chumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANGAZA"," userResponse":" MWANGAZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657561595","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657561595"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa umbali aliona mwangaza ukitokezea chumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKITOKEZEA"," userResponse":" UKITOKEZEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657562970","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657562969"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa umbali aliona mwangaza ukitokezea chumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUMBANI"," userResponse":" CHUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657566185","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657566185"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliharakisha kuelekea chumba hicho na kubisha hodi mlangoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIHARAKISHA"," userResponse":" ALIHARAKISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657567482","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657567482"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliharakisha kuelekea chumba hicho na kubisha hodi mlangoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUELEKEA"," userResponse":" KUELEKEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657567926","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657567926"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliharakisha kuelekea chumba hicho na kubisha hodi mlangoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUMBA"," userResponse":" CHUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657568551","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657568550"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliharakisha kuelekea chumba hicho na kubisha hodi mlangoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HICHO"," userResponse":" HICHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657569064","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657569064"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliharakisha kuelekea chumba hicho na kubisha hodi mlangoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657569937","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657569937"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliharakisha kuelekea chumba hicho na kubisha hodi mlangoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBISHA"," userResponse":" KUBISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657570381","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657570381"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliharakisha kuelekea chumba hicho na kubisha hodi mlangoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HODI"," userResponse":" HODI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657571388","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657571387"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliharakisha kuelekea chumba hicho na kubisha hodi mlangoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLANGONI"," userResponse":" MLANGONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657574308","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657574308"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La kushangaza ni kuwa mbwa ndiye aliufungua mlango na kusema Unataka nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657575543","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657575543"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La kushangaza ni kuwa mbwa ndiye aliufungua mlango na kusema Unataka nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSHANGAZA"," userResponse":" KUSHANGAZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657575807","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657575807"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La kushangaza ni kuwa mbwa ndiye aliufungua mlango na kusema Unataka nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657576546","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657576546"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La kushangaza ni kuwa mbwa ndiye aliufungua mlango na kusema Unataka nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657577595","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657577594"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La kushangaza ni kuwa mbwa ndiye aliufungua mlango na kusema Unataka nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBWA"," userResponse":" MBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657578412","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657578411"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La kushangaza ni kuwa mbwa ndiye aliufungua mlango na kusema Unataka nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIYE"," userResponse":" NDIYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657579488","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657579487"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La kushangaza ni kuwa mbwa ndiye aliufungua mlango na kusema Unataka nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIUFUNGUA"," userResponse":" ALIUFUNGUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657580161","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657580161"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La kushangaza ni kuwa mbwa ndiye aliufungua mlango na kusema Unataka nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLANGO"," userResponse":" MLANGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657580348","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657580346"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La kushangaza ni kuwa mbwa ndiye aliufungua mlango na kusema Unataka nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657581026","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657581025"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La kushangaza ni kuwa mbwa ndiye aliufungua mlango na kusema Unataka nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSEMA"," userResponse":" KUSEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657582482","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657582482"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La kushangaza ni kuwa mbwa ndiye aliufungua mlango na kusema Unataka nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNATAKA"," userResponse":" UNATAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657583096","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657583095"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La kushangaza ni kuwa mbwa ndiye aliufungua mlango na kusema Unataka nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657586269","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657586268"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimepotea nahitaji mahali pa kulala Nozibele alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIMEPOTEA"," userResponse":" NIMEPOTEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657587577","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657587576"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimepotea nahitaji mahali pa kulala Nozibele alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAHITAJI"," userResponse":" NAHITAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657588266","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657588265"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimepotea nahitaji mahali pa kulala Nozibele alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHALI"," userResponse":" MAHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657588558","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657588558"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimepotea nahitaji mahali pa kulala Nozibele alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PA"," userResponse":" PA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657589504","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657589503"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimepotea nahitaji mahali pa kulala Nozibele alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULALA"," userResponse":" KULALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657590846","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657590845"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimepotea nahitaji mahali pa kulala Nozibele alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NOZIBELE"," userResponse":" NOZIBELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657591873","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657591872"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimepotea nahitaji mahali pa kulala Nozibele alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657594381","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657594380"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbwa akajibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INGIA"," userResponse":" INGIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657594995","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657594994"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbwa akajibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" NDANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657595667","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657595666"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbwa akajibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AU"," userResponse":" AU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657596271","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657596271"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbwa akajibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIKUUME"," userResponse":" NIKUUME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657599103","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657599102"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbwa akajibu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBWA"," userResponse":" MBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657599992","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657599992"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbwa akajibu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAJIBU"," userResponse":" AKAJIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657603246","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657603246"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nozibele aliingia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NOZIBELE"," userResponse":" NOZIBELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657604424","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657604420"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nozibele aliingia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIINGIA"," userResponse":" ALIINGIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657607651","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657607651"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha mbwa akasema Nipikie chakula!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" KISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657607940","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657607940"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha mbwa akasema Nipikie chakula!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBWA"," userResponse":" MBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657608845","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657608845"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha mbwa akasema Nipikie chakula!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" AKASEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657609946","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657609945"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha mbwa akasema Nipikie chakula!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIPIKIE"," userResponse":" NIPIKIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657610744","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657610744"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha mbwa akasema Nipikie chakula!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657613255","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657613255"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sijawahi kumpikia mbwa chakula Nozibele aljibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657614159","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657614159"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sijawahi kumpikia mbwa chakula Nozibele aljibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIJAWAHI"," userResponse":" SIJAWAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657615213","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657615213"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sijawahi kumpikia mbwa chakula Nozibele aljibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMPIKIA"," userResponse":" KUMPIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657615701","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657615701"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sijawahi kumpikia mbwa chakula Nozibele aljibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBWA"," userResponse":" MBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657616898","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657616898"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sijawahi kumpikia mbwa chakula Nozibele aljibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657618241","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657618241"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sijawahi kumpikia mbwa chakula Nozibele aljibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NOZIBELE"," userResponse":" NOZIBELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657618993","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657618993"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sijawahi kumpikia mbwa chakula Nozibele aljibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALJIBU"," userResponse":" ALJIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657621338","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657621337"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbwa akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PIKA"," userResponse":" PIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657621789","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657621788"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbwa akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AU"," userResponse":" AU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657622456","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657622455"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbwa akasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIKUUME"," userResponse":" NIKUUME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657624835","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657624834"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbwa akasema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBWA"," userResponse":" MBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657625858","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657625858"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbwa akasema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" AKASEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657628617","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657628617"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nozibele alimpikia mbwa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NOZIBELE"," userResponse":" NOZIBELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657630044","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657630044"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nozibele alimpikia mbwa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMPIKIA"," userResponse":" ALIMPIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657630515","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657630515"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nozibele alimpikia mbwa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBWA"," userResponse":" MBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657631432","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657631428"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nozibele alimpikia mbwa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657634318","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657634318"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha mbwa akasema Nitayarishie kitanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" KISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657634938","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657634938"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha mbwa akasema Nitayarishie kitanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBWA"," userResponse":" MBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657635792","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657635792"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha mbwa akasema Nitayarishie kitanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" AKASEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657637352","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657637352"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha mbwa akasema Nitayarishie kitanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITAYARISHIE"," userResponse":" NITAYARISHIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657638122","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657638122"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha mbwa akasema Nitayarishie kitanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITANDA"," userResponse":" KITANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657641044","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657641043"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nozibele akajibu Sijawahi kumtayarishia mbwa kitanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NOZIBELE"," userResponse":" NOZIBELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657642096","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657642095"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nozibele akajibu Sijawahi kumtayarishia mbwa kitanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAJIBU"," userResponse":" AKAJIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657643597","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657643596"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nozibele akajibu Sijawahi kumtayarishia mbwa kitanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIJAWAHI"," userResponse":" SIJAWAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657645297","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657645297"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nozibele akajibu Sijawahi kumtayarishia mbwa kitanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMTAYARISHIA"," userResponse":" KUMTAYARISHIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657645882","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657645881"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nozibele akajibu Sijawahi kumtayarishia mbwa kitanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBWA"," userResponse":" MBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657647145","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657647144"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nozibele akajibu Sijawahi kumtayarishia mbwa kitanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITANDA"," userResponse":" KITANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657649979","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657649978"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbwa alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAYARISHA"," userResponse":" TAYARISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657650305","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657650305"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbwa alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AU"," userResponse":" AU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657651230","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657651230"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbwa alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIKUUME"," userResponse":" NIKUUME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657654107","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657654106"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbwa alisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBWA"," userResponse":" MBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657655029","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657655029"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbwa alisema."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657657846","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657657845"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nozibele alitayarisha kitanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NOZIBELE"," userResponse":" NOZIBELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657659326","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657659326"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nozibele alitayarisha kitanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITAYARISHA"," userResponse":" ALITAYARISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657660197","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657660197"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nozibele alitayarisha kitanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITANDA"," userResponse":" KITANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657663865","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657663864"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitakiwa kumpikia kumfagilia na kumwoshea mbwa kila siku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITAKIWA"," userResponse":" ALITAKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657665383","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657665383"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitakiwa kumpikia kumfagilia na kumwoshea mbwa kila siku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMPIKIA"," userResponse":" KUMPIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657667797","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657667796"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitakiwa kumpikia kumfagilia na kumwoshea mbwa kila siku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMFAGILIA"," userResponse":" KUMFAGILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657668498","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657668497"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitakiwa kumpikia kumfagilia na kumwoshea mbwa kila siku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657669655","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657669655"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitakiwa kumpikia kumfagilia na kumwoshea mbwa kila siku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMWOSHEA"," userResponse":" KUMWOSHEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657670167","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657670167"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitakiwa kumpikia kumfagilia na kumwoshea mbwa kila siku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBWA"," userResponse":" MBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657671195","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657671195"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitakiwa kumpikia kumfagilia na kumwoshea mbwa kila siku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657672051","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657672051"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitakiwa kumpikia kumfagilia na kumwoshea mbwa kila siku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657674294","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657674291"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha siku moja mbwa alisema Nozibele leo nalazimika kuwatembelea marafiki zangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" KISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657674851","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657674851"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha siku moja mbwa alisema Nozibele leo nalazimika kuwatembelea marafiki zangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657675392","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657675392"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha siku moja mbwa alisema Nozibele leo nalazimika kuwatembelea marafiki zangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657675955","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657675955"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha siku moja mbwa alisema Nozibele leo nalazimika kuwatembelea marafiki zangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBWA"," userResponse":" MBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657676883","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657676882"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha siku moja mbwa alisema Nozibele leo nalazimika kuwatembelea marafiki zangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657678308","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657678308"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha siku moja mbwa alisema Nozibele leo nalazimika kuwatembelea marafiki zangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NOZIBELE"," userResponse":" NOZIBELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657679737","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657679736"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha siku moja mbwa alisema Nozibele leo nalazimika kuwatembelea marafiki zangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LEO"," userResponse":" LEO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657680929","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657680928"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha siku moja mbwa alisema Nozibele leo nalazimika kuwatembelea marafiki zangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NALAZIMIKA"," userResponse":" NALAZIMIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657682303","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657682303"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha siku moja mbwa alisema Nozibele leo nalazimika kuwatembelea marafiki zangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWATEMBELEA"," userResponse":" KUWATEMBELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657683343","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657683343"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha siku moja mbwa alisema Nozibele leo nalazimika kuwatembelea marafiki zangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARAFIKI"," userResponse":" MARAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657683992","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657683991"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha siku moja mbwa alisema Nozibele leo nalazimika kuwatembelea marafiki zangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZANGU"," userResponse":" ZANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657686624","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657686624"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fagia nyumba pika chakula na uoshe vitu vyangu kabla sijarudi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAGIA"," userResponse":" FAGIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657687218","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657687217"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fagia nyumba pika chakula na uoshe vitu vyangu kabla sijarudi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657688706","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657688705"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fagia nyumba pika chakula na uoshe vitu vyangu kabla sijarudi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PIKA"," userResponse":" PIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657689712","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657689711"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fagia nyumba pika chakula na uoshe vitu vyangu kabla sijarudi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657690585","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657690584"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fagia nyumba pika chakula na uoshe vitu vyangu kabla sijarudi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657691100","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657691100"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fagia nyumba pika chakula na uoshe vitu vyangu kabla sijarudi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UOSHE"," userResponse":" UOSHE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657691683","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657691682"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fagia nyumba pika chakula na uoshe vitu vyangu kabla sijarudi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITU"," userResponse":" VITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657692227","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657692227"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fagia nyumba pika chakula na uoshe vitu vyangu kabla sijarudi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYANGU"," userResponse":" VYANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657693041","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657693039"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fagia nyumba pika chakula na uoshe vitu vyangu kabla sijarudi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KABLA"," userResponse":" KABLA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657694104","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657694104"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fagia nyumba pika chakula na uoshe vitu vyangu kabla sijarudi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIJARUDI"," userResponse":" SIJARUDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657697095","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657697095"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa alipoenda tu Nozibele alichukuwa nywele tatu kutoka kichwa chake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBWA"," userResponse":" MBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657698283","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657698283"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa alipoenda tu Nozibele alichukuwa nywele tatu kutoka kichwa chake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOENDA"," userResponse":" ALIPOENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657698770","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657698769"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa alipoenda tu Nozibele alichukuwa nywele tatu kutoka kichwa chake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TU"," userResponse":" TU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657700161","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657700160"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa alipoenda tu Nozibele alichukuwa nywele tatu kutoka kichwa chake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NOZIBELE"," userResponse":" NOZIBELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657701462","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657701462"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa alipoenda tu Nozibele alichukuwa nywele tatu kutoka kichwa chake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALICHUKUWA"," userResponse":" ALICHUKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657702061","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657702060"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa alipoenda tu Nozibele alichukuwa nywele tatu kutoka kichwa chake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYWELE"," userResponse":" NYWELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657702706","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657702705"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa alipoenda tu Nozibele alichukuwa nywele tatu kutoka kichwa chake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657703476","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657703476"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa alipoenda tu Nozibele alichukuwa nywele tatu kutoka kichwa chake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657704071","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657704071"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa alipoenda tu Nozibele alichukuwa nywele tatu kutoka kichwa chake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHWA"," userResponse":" KICHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657704697","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657704696"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa alipoenda tu Nozibele alichukuwa nywele tatu kutoka kichwa chake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKE"," userResponse":" CHAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657707512","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657707510"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliweka mmoja mvunguni mwa kitanda mwingine nyuma ya mlango na mwingine ndani ya boma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWEKA"," userResponse":" ALIWEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657708354","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657708354"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliweka mmoja mvunguni mwa kitanda mwingine nyuma ya mlango na mwingine ndani ya boma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657709335","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657709335"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliweka mmoja mvunguni mwa kitanda mwingine nyuma ya mlango na mwingine ndani ya boma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MVUNGUNI"," userResponse":" MVUNGUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657709612","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657709612"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliweka mmoja mvunguni mwa kitanda mwingine nyuma ya mlango na mwingine ndani ya boma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWA"," userResponse":" MWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657710657","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657710657"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliweka mmoja mvunguni mwa kitanda mwingine nyuma ya mlango na mwingine ndani ya boma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITANDA"," userResponse":" KITANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657712374","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657712373"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliweka mmoja mvunguni mwa kitanda mwingine nyuma ya mlango na mwingine ndani ya boma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINGINE"," userResponse":" MWINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657712905","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657712905"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliweka mmoja mvunguni mwa kitanda mwingine nyuma ya mlango na mwingine ndani ya boma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMA"," userResponse":" NYUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657713238","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657713238"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliweka mmoja mvunguni mwa kitanda mwingine nyuma ya mlango na mwingine ndani ya boma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657714183","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657714183"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliweka mmoja mvunguni mwa kitanda mwingine nyuma ya mlango na mwingine ndani ya boma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLANGO"," userResponse":" MLANGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657714985","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657714985"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliweka mmoja mvunguni mwa kitanda mwingine nyuma ya mlango na mwingine ndani ya boma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657715788","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657715788"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliweka mmoja mvunguni mwa kitanda mwingine nyuma ya mlango na mwingine ndani ya boma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINGINE"," userResponse":" MWINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657716441","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657716441"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliweka mmoja mvunguni mwa kitanda mwingine nyuma ya mlango na mwingine ndani ya boma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" NDANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657716591","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657716590"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliweka mmoja mvunguni mwa kitanda mwingine nyuma ya mlango na mwingine ndani ya boma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657717234","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657717233"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliweka mmoja mvunguni mwa kitanda mwingine nyuma ya mlango na mwingine ndani ya boma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BOMA"," userResponse":" BOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657719723","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657719722"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha alikimbia kwenda nyumbani haraka alivyoweza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" KISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657721237","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657721236"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha alikimbia kwenda nyumbani haraka alivyoweza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKIMBIA"," userResponse":" ALIKIMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657721709","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657721708"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha alikimbia kwenda nyumbani haraka alivyoweza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657722460","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657722458"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha alikimbia kwenda nyumbani haraka alivyoweza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657723653","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657723653"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha alikimbia kwenda nyumbani haraka alivyoweza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARAKA"," userResponse":" HARAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657724738","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657724738"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha alikimbia kwenda nyumbani haraka alivyoweza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIVYOWEZA"," userResponse":" ALIVYOWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657727649","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657727649"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa aliporudi alimtafuta Nozibele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBWA"," userResponse":" MBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657729046","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657729046"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa aliporudi alimtafuta Nozibele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPORUDI"," userResponse":" ALIPORUDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657731065","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657731064"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa aliporudi alimtafuta Nozibele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMTAFUTA"," userResponse":" ALIMTAFUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657732079","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657732078"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa aliporudi alimtafuta Nozibele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NOZIBELE"," userResponse":" NOZIBELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657735167","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657735167"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" aliita kwa sauti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NOZIBELE"," userResponse":" NOZIBELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657736257","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657736257"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" aliita kwa sauti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKO"," userResponse":" UKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657736914","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657736913"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" aliita kwa sauti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAPI"," userResponse":" WAPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657739977","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657739977"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" aliita kwa sauti."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIITA"," userResponse":" ALIITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657740280","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657740280"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" aliita kwa sauti."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657741083","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657741082"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" aliita kwa sauti."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657743474","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657743473"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko hapa mvunguni mwa kitanda unywele wa kwanza ulisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIKO"," userResponse":" NIKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657744037","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657744037"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko hapa mvunguni mwa kitanda unywele wa kwanza ulisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPA"," userResponse":" HAPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657745078","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657745077"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko hapa mvunguni mwa kitanda unywele wa kwanza ulisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MVUNGUNI"," userResponse":" MVUNGUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657745255","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657745252"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko hapa mvunguni mwa kitanda unywele wa kwanza ulisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWA"," userResponse":" MWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657746194","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657746194"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko hapa mvunguni mwa kitanda unywele wa kwanza ulisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITANDA"," userResponse":" KITANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657747353","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657747352"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko hapa mvunguni mwa kitanda unywele wa kwanza ulisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNYWELE"," userResponse":" UNYWELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657747668","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657747668"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko hapa mvunguni mwa kitanda unywele wa kwanza ulisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657748774","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657748773"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko hapa mvunguni mwa kitanda unywele wa kwanza ulisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657749761","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657749760"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko hapa mvunguni mwa kitanda unywele wa kwanza ulisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULISEMA"," userResponse":" ULISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657752123","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657752122"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko hapa nyuma ya mlango unywele wa pili ukasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIKO"," userResponse":" NIKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657752615","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657752615"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko hapa nyuma ya mlango unywele wa pili ukasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPA"," userResponse":" HAPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657753158","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657753158"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko hapa nyuma ya mlango unywele wa pili ukasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMA"," userResponse":" NYUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657753454","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657753454"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko hapa nyuma ya mlango unywele wa pili ukasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657754330","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657754330"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko hapa nyuma ya mlango unywele wa pili ukasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLANGO"," userResponse":" MLANGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657755338","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657755337"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko hapa nyuma ya mlango unywele wa pili ukasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNYWELE"," userResponse":" UNYWELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657755605","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657755604"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko hapa nyuma ya mlango unywele wa pili ukasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657756324","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657756323"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko hapa nyuma ya mlango unywele wa pili ukasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PILI"," userResponse":" PILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657757375","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657757375"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko hapa nyuma ya mlango unywele wa pili ukasema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKASEMA"," userResponse":" UKASEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657759803","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657759803"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko hapa ndani ya boma ukasema unywele wa tatu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIKO"," userResponse":" NIKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657760335","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657760334"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko hapa ndani ya boma ukasema unywele wa tatu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPA"," userResponse":" HAPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657761265","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657761265"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko hapa ndani ya boma ukasema unywele wa tatu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" NDANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657761369","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657761369"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko hapa ndani ya boma ukasema unywele wa tatu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657761954","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657761954"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko hapa ndani ya boma ukasema unywele wa tatu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BOMA"," userResponse":" BOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657763381","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657763380"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko hapa ndani ya boma ukasema unywele wa tatu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKASEMA"," userResponse":" UKASEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657764163","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657764162"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko hapa ndani ya boma ukasema unywele wa tatu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNYWELE"," userResponse":" UNYWELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657764349","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657764348"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko hapa ndani ya boma ukasema unywele wa tatu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657764995","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657764994"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko hapa ndani ya boma ukasema unywele wa tatu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657767862","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657767862"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Papo hapo mbwa alifahamu kuwa Nozibele alikuwa amemdanganya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAPO"," userResponse":" PAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657768548","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657768547"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Papo hapo mbwa alifahamu kuwa Nozibele alikuwa amemdanganya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657769471","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657769471"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Papo hapo mbwa alifahamu kuwa Nozibele alikuwa amemdanganya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBWA"," userResponse":" MBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657770606","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657770605"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Papo hapo mbwa alifahamu kuwa Nozibele alikuwa amemdanganya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFAHAMU"," userResponse":" ALIFAHAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657771020","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657771019"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Papo hapo mbwa alifahamu kuwa Nozibele alikuwa amemdanganya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657771999","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657771998"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Papo hapo mbwa alifahamu kuwa Nozibele alikuwa amemdanganya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NOZIBELE"," userResponse":" NOZIBELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657772899","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657772899"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Papo hapo mbwa alifahamu kuwa Nozibele alikuwa amemdanganya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657774383","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657774383"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Papo hapo mbwa alifahamu kuwa Nozibele alikuwa amemdanganya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEMDANGANYA"," userResponse":" AMEMDANGANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657776405","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657776405"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alikimbia moja kwa moja hadi kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657777170","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657777169"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alikimbia moja kwa moja hadi kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657778260","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657778260"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alikimbia moja kwa moja hadi kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKIMBIA"," userResponse":" ALIKIMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657778831","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657778831"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alikimbia moja kwa moja hadi kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657779088","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657779087"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alikimbia moja kwa moja hadi kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657779581","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657779581"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alikimbia moja kwa moja hadi kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657780062","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657780062"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alikimbia moja kwa moja hadi kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657781161","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657781161"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alikimbia moja kwa moja hadi kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJINI"," userResponse":" KIJIJINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657783829","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657783828"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ndugu zake Nozibele walikuwa wamemsubiri kwa fimbo kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657784312","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657784311"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ndugu zake Nozibele walikuwa wamemsubiri kwa fimbo kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDUGU"," userResponse":" NDUGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657784776","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657784775"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ndugu zake Nozibele walikuwa wamemsubiri kwa fimbo kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657785776","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657785776"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ndugu zake Nozibele walikuwa wamemsubiri kwa fimbo kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NOZIBELE"," userResponse":" NOZIBELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657786892","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657786892"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ndugu zake Nozibele walikuwa wamemsubiri kwa fimbo kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657788002","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657788002"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ndugu zake Nozibele walikuwa wamemsubiri kwa fimbo kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAMEMSUBIRI"," userResponse":" WAMEMSUBIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657788296","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657788296"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ndugu zake Nozibele walikuwa wamemsubiri kwa fimbo kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657789072","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657789071"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ndugu zake Nozibele walikuwa wamemsubiri kwa fimbo kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FIMBO"," userResponse":" FIMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657789798","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657789797"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ndugu zake Nozibele walikuwa wamemsubiri kwa fimbo kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657792101","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657792101"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa aligeuka na kukimbia na hadi leo hajawahi kuonekana tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBWA"," userResponse":" MBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657793146","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657793146"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa aligeuka na kukimbia na hadi leo hajawahi kuonekana tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIGEUKA"," userResponse":" ALIGEUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657793350","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657793350"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa aligeuka na kukimbia na hadi leo hajawahi kuonekana tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657794879","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657794878"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa aligeuka na kukimbia na hadi leo hajawahi kuonekana tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKIMBIA"," userResponse":" KUKIMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657795737","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657795737"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa aligeuka na kukimbia na hadi leo hajawahi kuonekana tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657796161","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657796160"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa aligeuka na kukimbia na hadi leo hajawahi kuonekana tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657796621","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657796621"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa aligeuka na kukimbia na hadi leo hajawahi kuonekana tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LEO"," userResponse":" LEO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657797776","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657797776"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa aligeuka na kukimbia na hadi leo hajawahi kuonekana tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAJAWAHI"," userResponse":" HAJAWAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657798784","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657798783"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa aligeuka na kukimbia na hadi leo hajawahi kuonekana tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUONEKANA"," userResponse":" KUONEKANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657799386","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657799386"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa aligeuka na kukimbia na hadi leo hajawahi kuonekana tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657801990","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657801988"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Mbwa aligeuka na kukimbia na hadi leo hajawahi kuonekana tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657802090","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657802090"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa aligeuka na kukimbia na hadi leo hajawahi kuonekana tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:N..N.all.rand.all.stat.show.104","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657809099","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657809099"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbwa aligeuka na kukimbia na hadi leo hajawahi kuonekana tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..20.off2.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657814259","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657814259"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbwa aligeuka na kukimbia na hadi leo hajawahi kuonekana tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657821003","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657821003"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbwa aligeuka na kukimbia na hadi leo hajawahi kuonekana tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657828593","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657828593"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbwa aligeuka na kukimbia na hadi leo hajawahi kuonekana tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:N..N.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.105","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657838772","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657838771"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbwa aligeuka na kukimbia na hadi leo hajawahi kuonekana tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657843666","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657843666"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbwa aligeuka na kukimbia na hadi leo hajawahi kuonekana tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:N..N.all.10.rand.say.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657849133","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657849132"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbwa aligeuka na kukimbia na hadi leo hajawahi kuonekana tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_63","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657869365","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657869365"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" a66394c6-7f52-45ba-a6c4-b207b851d5ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbwa aligeuka na kukimbia na hadi leo hajawahi kuonekana tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657869439","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657869438"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 793c1d58-f7c0-4840-9f92-2cfdfc01ccaa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_63"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja alikwenda msituni kwa matembezi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657877075","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657877075"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 793c1d58-f7c0-4840-9f92-2cfdfc01ccaa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_63"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Siku moja alikwenda msituni kwa matembezi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.decr.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657882638","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657882637"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 793c1d58-f7c0-4840-9f92-2cfdfc01ccaa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_63"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Siku moja alikwenda msituni kwa matembezi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657889012","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657889012"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 793c1d58-f7c0-4840-9f92-2cfdfc01ccaa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_63"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Siku moja alikwenda msituni kwa matembezi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657895869","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657895868"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 793c1d58-f7c0-4840-9f92-2cfdfc01ccaa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_63"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Siku moja alikwenda msituni kwa matembezi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657903958","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657903958"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 793c1d58-f7c0-4840-9f92-2cfdfc01ccaa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_63"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Siku moja alikwenda msituni kwa matembezi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:9..19.off1.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657909465","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657909464"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 793c1d58-f7c0-4840-9f92-2cfdfc01ccaa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_63"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Siku moja alikwenda msituni kwa matembezi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657914783","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657914783"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 793c1d58-f7c0-4840-9f92-2cfdfc01ccaa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_63"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Siku moja alikwenda msituni kwa matembezi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657919670","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657919670"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 793c1d58-f7c0-4840-9f92-2cfdfc01ccaa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_63"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Siku moja alikwenda msituni kwa matembezi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657925584","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657925584"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 793c1d58-f7c0-4840-9f92-2cfdfc01ccaa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_63"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Siku moja alikwenda msituni kwa matembezi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.decr.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657930376","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657930376"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 793c1d58-f7c0-4840-9f92-2cfdfc01ccaa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_63"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Siku moja alikwenda msituni kwa matembezi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657936367","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657936367"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 793c1d58-f7c0-4840-9f92-2cfdfc01ccaa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_63"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Siku moja alikwenda msituni kwa matembezi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657941836","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657941836"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 793c1d58-f7c0-4840-9f92-2cfdfc01ccaa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_63"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Siku moja alikwenda msituni kwa matembezi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.54__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657953047","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657953047"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 1d3cf321-f75f-4502-97e8-56708fad9e82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.54__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" omba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBA"," userResponse":" OMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.54__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657956443","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657956443"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 1d3cf321-f75f-4502-97e8-56708fad9e82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.54__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" omba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.54__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657958017","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657958017"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 1d3cf321-f75f-4502-97e8-56708fad9e82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.54__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ovaroli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OVAROLI"," userResponse":" OVAROLI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.54__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657961655","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657961655"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 1d3cf321-f75f-4502-97e8-56708fad9e82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.54__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ovaroli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OVAROLI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.54__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657963226","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657963226"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 1d3cf321-f75f-4502-97e8-56708fad9e82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.54__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ona"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ONA"," userResponse":" ONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.54__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657966433","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657966433"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 1d3cf321-f75f-4502-97e8-56708fad9e82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.54__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ona"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ONA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.54__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657967994","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657967993"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 1d3cf321-f75f-4502-97e8-56708fad9e82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.54__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" oa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OA"," userResponse":" OA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.54__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657971104","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657971104"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 1d3cf321-f75f-4502-97e8-56708fad9e82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.54__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" oa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.54__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657972672","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657972672"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 1d3cf321-f75f-4502-97e8-56708fad9e82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.54__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" osha"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OSHA"," userResponse":" OSHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.54__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657976176","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657976176"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 1d3cf321-f75f-4502-97e8-56708fad9e82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.54__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" osha"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OSHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.54__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657977739","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657977739"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 1d3cf321-f75f-4502-97e8-56708fad9e82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.54__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ofisi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OFISI"," userResponse":" OFISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.54__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657981683","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657981683"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 1d3cf321-f75f-4502-97e8-56708fad9e82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.54__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ofisi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OFISI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.54__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657983236","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657983236"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 1d3cf321-f75f-4502-97e8-56708fad9e82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.54__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ogelea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OGELEA"," userResponse":" OGELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.54__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657987436","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657987436"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 1d3cf321-f75f-4502-97e8-56708fad9e82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.54__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ogelea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OGELEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.54__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657989451","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657989451"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 1d3cf321-f75f-4502-97e8-56708fad9e82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.54__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" ogelea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657989617","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657989617"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 1d3cf321-f75f-4502-97e8-56708fad9e82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.54__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ogelea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OGELEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:9..19.off1.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548657997191","data":{"timestamp":" 1548657997191"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 1d3cf321-f75f-4502-97e8-56708fad9e82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.54__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ogelea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.106","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658008176","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658008176"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 71c6da94-3f98-4d35-a3a1-f4ec6468ccb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.106"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_o-e-r"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.106","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658011648","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658011648"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 71c6da94-3f98-4d35-a3a1-f4ec6468ccb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.106"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_t-o-v"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.106","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658014428","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658014427"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 71c6da94-3f98-4d35-a3a1-f4ec6468ccb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.106"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_o-w-t"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.106","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658017268","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658017267"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 71c6da94-3f98-4d35-a3a1-f4ec6468ccb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.106"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_o-t-b"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.106","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658021048","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658021047"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 71c6da94-3f98-4d35-a3a1-f4ec6468ccb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.106"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_h-p-o"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.106","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658024752","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658024752"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 71c6da94-3f98-4d35-a3a1-f4ec6468ccb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.106"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_o-m-u"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.106","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658041231","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658041231"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 71c6da94-3f98-4d35-a3a1-f4ec6468ccb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.106"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_f-m-o"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.106","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658044873","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658044873"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 71c6da94-3f98-4d35-a3a1-f4ec6468ccb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.106"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_o-a-h"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.106","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658048414","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658048414"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 71c6da94-3f98-4d35-a3a1-f4ec6468ccb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.106"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_y-o-v"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.106","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658051537","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658051537"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 71c6da94-3f98-4d35-a3a1-f4ec6468ccb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.106"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_ch-o-e"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.106","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658057308","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658057307"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 71c6da94-3f98-4d35-a3a1-f4ec6468ccb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.106"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_o_ch-o-e"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_63","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658063631","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658063630"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 71c6da94-3f98-4d35-a3a1-f4ec6468ccb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.106"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_o_ch-o-e"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:O..O.all.10.rand.say.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658073104","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658073104"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 71c6da94-3f98-4d35-a3a1-f4ec6468ccb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.106"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_o_ch-o-e"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.decr.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658090845","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658090845"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 71c6da94-3f98-4d35-a3a1-f4ec6468ccb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.106"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_o_ch-o-e"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658103853","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658103853"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3a60d5f8-350d-44d9-b85d-46bd0d822638"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658105864","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658105864"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3a60d5f8-350d-44d9-b85d-46bd0d822638"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658107462","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658107462"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3a60d5f8-350d-44d9-b85d-46bd0d822638"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658110806","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658110806"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3a60d5f8-350d-44d9-b85d-46bd0d822638"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658112387","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658112387"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3a60d5f8-350d-44d9-b85d-46bd0d822638"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658114731","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658114731"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3a60d5f8-350d-44d9-b85d-46bd0d822638"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658116292","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658116292"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3a60d5f8-350d-44d9-b85d-46bd0d822638"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658119176","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658119176"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3a60d5f8-350d-44d9-b85d-46bd0d822638"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658120752","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658120752"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3a60d5f8-350d-44d9-b85d-46bd0d822638"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658122933","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658122933"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3a60d5f8-350d-44d9-b85d-46bd0d822638"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658124547","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658124546"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3a60d5f8-350d-44d9-b85d-46bd0d822638"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658128410","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658128410"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3a60d5f8-350d-44d9-b85d-46bd0d822638"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658129994","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658129994"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3a60d5f8-350d-44d9-b85d-46bd0d822638"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658132018","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658132018"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3a60d5f8-350d-44d9-b85d-46bd0d822638"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658133594","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658133594"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3a60d5f8-350d-44d9-b85d-46bd0d822638"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658135650","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658135650"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3a60d5f8-350d-44d9-b85d-46bd0d822638"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658137239","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658137239"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3a60d5f8-350d-44d9-b85d-46bd0d822638"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658144604","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658144604"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3a60d5f8-350d-44d9-b85d-46bd0d822638"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658146169","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658146169"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3a60d5f8-350d-44d9-b85d-46bd0d822638"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658148308","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658148308"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3a60d5f8-350d-44d9-b85d-46bd0d822638"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658149858","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658149858"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3a60d5f8-350d-44d9-b85d-46bd0d822638"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658152136","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658152135"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3a60d5f8-350d-44d9-b85d-46bd0d822638"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658153710","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658153710"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3a60d5f8-350d-44d9-b85d-46bd0d822638"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658155950","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658155949"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3a60d5f8-350d-44d9-b85d-46bd0d822638"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658157544","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658157543"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3a60d5f8-350d-44d9-b85d-46bd0d822638"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" m"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658159716","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658159716"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3a60d5f8-350d-44d9-b85d-46bd0d822638"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" m"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658161320","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658161320"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3a60d5f8-350d-44d9-b85d-46bd0d822638"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658163448","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658163447"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3a60d5f8-350d-44d9-b85d-46bd0d822638"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658165043","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658165043"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3a60d5f8-350d-44d9-b85d-46bd0d822638"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658167290","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658167290"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3a60d5f8-350d-44d9-b85d-46bd0d822638"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658168854","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658168854"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3a60d5f8-350d-44d9-b85d-46bd0d822638"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658171070","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658171070"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3a60d5f8-350d-44d9-b85d-46bd0d822638"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658172654","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658172654"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3a60d5f8-350d-44d9-b85d-46bd0d822638"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658175095","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658175094"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3a60d5f8-350d-44d9-b85d-46bd0d822638"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658176666","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658176666"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3a60d5f8-350d-44d9-b85d-46bd0d822638"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658179895","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658179894"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3a60d5f8-350d-44d9-b85d-46bd0d822638"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658181486","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658181486"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3a60d5f8-350d-44d9-b85d-46bd0d822638"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658184689","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658184689"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3a60d5f8-350d-44d9-b85d-46bd0d822638"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658186291","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658186290"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3a60d5f8-350d-44d9-b85d-46bd0d822638"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658188362","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658188361"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3a60d5f8-350d-44d9-b85d-46bd0d822638"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658189947","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658189947"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3a60d5f8-350d-44d9-b85d-46bd0d822638"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658192765","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658192765"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3a60d5f8-350d-44d9-b85d-46bd0d822638"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658194366","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658194366"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3a60d5f8-350d-44d9-b85d-46bd0d822638"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658196548","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658196547"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3a60d5f8-350d-44d9-b85d-46bd0d822638"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658198148","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658198148"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3a60d5f8-350d-44d9-b85d-46bd0d822638"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658200316","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658200316"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3a60d5f8-350d-44d9-b85d-46bd0d822638"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658201894","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658201894"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3a60d5f8-350d-44d9-b85d-46bd0d822638"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658203950","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658203950"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3a60d5f8-350d-44d9-b85d-46bd0d822638"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658205959","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658205958"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3a60d5f8-350d-44d9-b85d-46bd0d822638"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658206054","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658206054"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3a60d5f8-350d-44d9-b85d-46bd0d822638"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658213315","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658213314"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3a60d5f8-350d-44d9-b85d-46bd0d822638"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658220109","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658220109"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3a60d5f8-350d-44d9-b85d-46bd0d822638"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658228673","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658228673"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3a60d5f8-350d-44d9-b85d-46bd0d822638"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658235841","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658235841"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3a60d5f8-350d-44d9-b85d-46bd0d822638"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658241664","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658241663"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3a60d5f8-350d-44d9-b85d-46bd0d822638"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:P..P.all.rand.all.stat.show.108","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658250069","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658250068"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3a60d5f8-350d-44d9-b85d-46bd0d822638"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.decr.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658256395","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658256394"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 3a60d5f8-350d-44d9-b85d-46bd0d822638"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658266381","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658266381"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 6a84d5a4-e69c-484e-a938-1f4b35471ac8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658266754","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658266754"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 6a84d5a4-e69c-484e-a938-1f4b35471ac8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658267238","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658267238"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 6a84d5a4-e69c-484e-a938-1f4b35471ac8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658267583","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658267583"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 6a84d5a4-e69c-484e-a938-1f4b35471ac8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658267986","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658267986"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 6a84d5a4-e69c-484e-a938-1f4b35471ac8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658268459","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658268459"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 6a84d5a4-e69c-484e-a938-1f4b35471ac8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658268681","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658268681"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 6a84d5a4-e69c-484e-a938-1f4b35471ac8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658271885","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658271885"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 6a84d5a4-e69c-484e-a938-1f4b35471ac8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658271918","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658271918"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 6a84d5a4-e69c-484e-a938-1f4b35471ac8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658272632","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658272632"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 6a84d5a4-e69c-484e-a938-1f4b35471ac8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658273026","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658273026"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 6a84d5a4-e69c-484e-a938-1f4b35471ac8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658273324","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658273324"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 6a84d5a4-e69c-484e-a938-1f4b35471ac8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658273529","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658273529"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 6a84d5a4-e69c-484e-a938-1f4b35471ac8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658273726","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658273725"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 6a84d5a4-e69c-484e-a938-1f4b35471ac8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658274041","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658274041"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 6a84d5a4-e69c-484e-a938-1f4b35471ac8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658274267","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658274267"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 6a84d5a4-e69c-484e-a938-1f4b35471ac8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658277464","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658277463"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 6a84d5a4-e69c-484e-a938-1f4b35471ac8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658277887","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658277887"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 6a84d5a4-e69c-484e-a938-1f4b35471ac8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658282087","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658282087"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 6a84d5a4-e69c-484e-a938-1f4b35471ac8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658282299","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658282298"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 6a84d5a4-e69c-484e-a938-1f4b35471ac8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658282509","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658282509"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 6a84d5a4-e69c-484e-a938-1f4b35471ac8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658286022","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658286022"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 6a84d5a4-e69c-484e-a938-1f4b35471ac8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658289770","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658289770"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 6a84d5a4-e69c-484e-a938-1f4b35471ac8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658290801","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658290801"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 6a84d5a4-e69c-484e-a938-1f4b35471ac8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658293513","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658293513"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 6a84d5a4-e69c-484e-a938-1f4b35471ac8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658293901","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658293901"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 6a84d5a4-e69c-484e-a938-1f4b35471ac8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658294392","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658294392"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 6a84d5a4-e69c-484e-a938-1f4b35471ac8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658294751","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658294751"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 6a84d5a4-e69c-484e-a938-1f4b35471ac8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658295162","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658295161"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 6a84d5a4-e69c-484e-a938-1f4b35471ac8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658295655","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658295654"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 6a84d5a4-e69c-484e-a938-1f4b35471ac8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658295887","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658295886"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 6a84d5a4-e69c-484e-a938-1f4b35471ac8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658299043","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658299043"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 6a84d5a4-e69c-484e-a938-1f4b35471ac8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658299078","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658299077"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 6a84d5a4-e69c-484e-a938-1f4b35471ac8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658299791","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658299791"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 6a84d5a4-e69c-484e-a938-1f4b35471ac8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658300186","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658300186"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 6a84d5a4-e69c-484e-a938-1f4b35471ac8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658300483","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658300483"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 6a84d5a4-e69c-484e-a938-1f4b35471ac8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658300691","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658300691"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 6a84d5a4-e69c-484e-a938-1f4b35471ac8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658300893","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658300893"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 6a84d5a4-e69c-484e-a938-1f4b35471ac8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658301215","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658301215"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 6a84d5a4-e69c-484e-a938-1f4b35471ac8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658301456","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658301456"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 6a84d5a4-e69c-484e-a938-1f4b35471ac8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658304095","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658304095"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 6a84d5a4-e69c-484e-a938-1f4b35471ac8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658304154","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658304154"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 6a84d5a4-e69c-484e-a938-1f4b35471ac8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658310329","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658310329"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 6a84d5a4-e69c-484e-a938-1f4b35471ac8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:P..P.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.109","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658329462","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658329462"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 6a84d5a4-e69c-484e-a938-1f4b35471ac8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658339543","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658339542"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 6a84d5a4-e69c-484e-a938-1f4b35471ac8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658354175","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658354175"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 6a84d5a4-e69c-484e-a938-1f4b35471ac8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658364974","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658364974"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 6a84d5a4-e69c-484e-a938-1f4b35471ac8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658373404","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658373403"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 6a84d5a4-e69c-484e-a938-1f4b35471ac8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:5..15.off1.3__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658381423","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658381422"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 6a84d5a4-e69c-484e-a938-1f4b35471ac8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658392996","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658392996"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 691e38ac-84fd-47fa-b6d9-c4f12d593ab3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_e-d-a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658396157","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658396157"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 691e38ac-84fd-47fa-b6d9-c4f12d593ab3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_d-b-p"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658399324","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658399324"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 691e38ac-84fd-47fa-b6d9-c4f12d593ab3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_u-f-ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658408612","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658408612"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 691e38ac-84fd-47fa-b6d9-c4f12d593ab3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_u-f-ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658412303","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658412303"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 691e38ac-84fd-47fa-b6d9-c4f12d593ab3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_p-b-d"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658420860","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658420860"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 691e38ac-84fd-47fa-b6d9-c4f12d593ab3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_p-b-d"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658424017","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658424016"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 691e38ac-84fd-47fa-b6d9-c4f12d593ab3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_c-e-o"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658427963","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658427963"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 691e38ac-84fd-47fa-b6d9-c4f12d593ab3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_t-f-r"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658431328","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658431328"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 691e38ac-84fd-47fa-b6d9-c4f12d593ab3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_o-g-j"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658434715","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658434715"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 691e38ac-84fd-47fa-b6d9-c4f12d593ab3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_h_h-n-u"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658438071","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658438071"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 691e38ac-84fd-47fa-b6d9-c4f12d593ab3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_j-l-i"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658441871","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658441871"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 691e38ac-84fd-47fa-b6d9-c4f12d593ab3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_i-l-j"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658445459","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658445459"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 691e38ac-84fd-47fa-b6d9-c4f12d593ab3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_k-f-r"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658448403","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658448403"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 691e38ac-84fd-47fa-b6d9-c4f12d593ab3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_l_l-j-i"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658451543","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658451542"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 691e38ac-84fd-47fa-b6d9-c4f12d593ab3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_m-w-n"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658455596","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658455596"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 691e38ac-84fd-47fa-b6d9-c4f12d593ab3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_u-m-n"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548658458808","data":{"timestamp":" 1548658458808"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_092218"," gameId":" 691e38ac-84fd-47fa-b6d9-c4f12d593ab3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_n_u-m-n"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}